<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dictionary xmlns="http://www.cfeclipse.org/version1/dictionary">			
	<tags>
		
				
				<tag name="cfswitch">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with cfcase and cfdefaultcase. Evaluates a passed expression and passes control to the 
  cfcase tag that matches the expression result. You can optionally code a cfdefaultcase tag, which 
  receives control if there is no matching cfcase tag value.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="expression">
							<help><![CDATA[Any CFML expression that yields a scalar value. CFML converts integers, real numbers, 
		Booleans, and dates to numeric values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfapplication">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines scoping for a application, enables or disables storing client variables, 
			and specifies a client variable storage mechanism. 
			By default, client variables are disabled. Also, enables session variables and sets timeouts 
			for session and application variables. Session and application variables are stored in memory.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for defaultdatasource]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of your application. This name can be up to 64 characters long.
   		Required for application and session variables, optional for client variables]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="loginstorage">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="securejsonprefix">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sessionmanagement">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes enables session variables. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="defaultdatasource">
							<help><![CDATA[the default datasource for this enviroment]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="applicationtimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter the CreateTimeSpan function and values in days, hours, minutes, and seconds, separated 
		by commas, to specify the lifespan of application variables. The default value is specified in
		the Variables page of the Railo Administrator.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="clientmanagement">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Enables client variables. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sessiontimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter the CreateTimeSpan function and values in days, hours, minutes, and seconds, separated 
		by commas, to specify the lifespan of session variables. The default value is specified in the
		Variables page of the Railo Administrator.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mappings">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scriptprotect">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to protect variables from cross-site scripting attacks]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="clientstorage">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies how Railo stores client variables]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="securejson">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="setclientcookies">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes enables client cookies. Default is Yes. If you set this attribute to 
		"No", Railo does not automatically send the CFID and CFTOKEN cookies to the client browser;
		you must manually code CFID and CFTOKEN on the URL for every page that uses Session or Client variables.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="customtagpaths">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="setdomaincookies">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Sets the CFID and CFTOKEN cookies for a domain, not just a single host. 
		Applications that are running on clusters must set this value to Yes. The default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfajaximport">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfreturn">
					<help><![CDATA[Returns result values from a component method. Contains an expression returned as result of the function.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="expr">
							<help><![CDATA[An expression; the result of the function from which this tag is called.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfbreak">
					<help><![CDATA[Used to break out of a cfloop,cfwhile or cfforeach.]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfmailparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Can either attach a file or add a header to a message. It is nested within a cfmail tag. You can 
  use more than one cfmailparam tag within a cfmail tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="remove">
							<help><![CDATA[remove attachment from filesystem after the mail is sucessful sended]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the header. Header names are case insensitive. This attribute is mutually 
		exclusive with the file attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[Attaches the specified file to the message. This attribute is mutually exclusive with the 
		name attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[The MIME media type of the part.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="content">
							<help><![CDATA[send given value as attachment]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates the value of the header.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="contentid">
							<help><![CDATA[The Identifier for the attached file. This ID should be globally unique and is used to identify the file in an IMG or other tag in the mail body that references the file content.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="disposition">
							<help><![CDATA[How the attached file is to be handled. Can be one of the following:
			attachment: presents the file as an attachment. 
			inline: displays the file contents in the message.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfreportparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Runs a predefined Crystal Reports report.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Variable name for data that is passed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Value of the data that is sent.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfthread">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="priority">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="retryinterval">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="duration">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="retryintervall">
							<help><![CDATA[deprecated, alias for retryInterval]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftransaction">
					<help><![CDATA[Groups multiple queries into a single unit. The cftransaction 
  tag provides commit and rollback processing.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="isolation">
							<help><![CDATA[ODBC lock type.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdirectory">
					<help><![CDATA[Handles interactions with directories.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Required for action = "list". Ignored by all other actions. Name of output query for directory 
		listing.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="recurse">
							<help><![CDATA[Whether Railo performs the action on subdirectories]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filter">
							<help><![CDATA[Optional for action = "list". Ignored by all other actions. File extension filter applied to
		returned names. For example: *m. Only one mask filter can be applied at a time.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Defines the action to be taken with directory(ies) specified in directory.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="serverpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[allow you to access filesystem, also when access is denied for your context]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="newdirectory">
							<help><![CDATA[Required for action = "rename". Ignored by all other actions. The new name of the directory 
		specified in the directory attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sort">
							<help><![CDATA[Optional for action = "list". Ignored by all other actions. The query columns by which to sort 
		the directory listing. Any combination of columns from query output can be specified in comma-separated list.
		You can specify ASC (ascending) or DESC (descending) as qualifiers for column names. ASC is the default]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mode">
							<help><![CDATA[Used with action = "Create" to define the permissions for a directory on UNIX and Linux 
		platforms. Ignored on Windows. Options correspond to the octal values of the UNIX chmod command. From 
		left to right, permissions are assigned for owner, group, and other.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="storage">
							<help><![CDATA[only used for S3 Resources]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="directory">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the directory to perform the action against.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="acl">
							<help><![CDATA[only used for S3 Resources]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="listinfo">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfrethrow">
					<help><![CDATA[Rethrows the currently active exception. Preserves the exception's cfcatch.type and cfcatch.
  agContext information.]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflog">
					<help><![CDATA[Writes a message to a log file.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="time">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to log the system time.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="date">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to log the system date.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="log">
							<help><![CDATA[If you omit the file attribute, specifies the standard log file in which to write the message. 
		Ignored if you specify a file attribute]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="thread">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to log the thread ID. The thread ID identifies which internal service thread logged a 
		message. Since a service thread normally services a CFML page request to completion, then moves on to 
		the next queued request, the thread ID serves as a rough indication of which request logged a message. 
		Leaving thread IDs turned on can help diagnose patterns of server activity.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[The type or severity of the message.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="application">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to log the application name if one has been specified in a cfapplication tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="text">
							<help><![CDATA[The message text to log.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfelse">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with cfelse and cfelseif, cfif lets you create simple and compound conditional statements 
	 in CFML. The value in the cfif tag can be any expression.]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfinvokeargument">
					<help><![CDATA[Argument for the Invoke Tag]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[name of the argument]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="omit">
							<help><![CDATA[Enables you to omit a parameter when invoking a web service]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[value of the argument]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfreport">
					<help><![CDATA[Runs a predefined Crystal Reports report.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="formula">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies one or more named formulas. Terminate each formula specification with a semicolon.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[The password that corresponds to a username required for database access. Overrides the default 
		settings for the data source in the Railo Administrator.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overwrite">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[The username required for entry into the database from which the report is created. Overrides 
		the default settings for the data source in the Railo Administrator.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="userpassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ownerpassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="permissions">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="orderby">
							<help><![CDATA[Orders results according to your specifications.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="encryption">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filename">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="report">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the report path. Store Crystal Reports files in the same directories as cfml templates.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="template">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the path to the report definition file, relative to the web root.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfschedule">
					<help><![CDATA[Provides a programmatic interface to the scheduling engine. You can run a specified 
  page at scheduled intervals with the option to write out static HTML pages. This lets you offer users 
  access to pages that publish data, such as reports, without forcing users to wait while a database transaction 
  is performed in order to populate the data on the page.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[Password if URL is protected.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returnvariable">
							<help><![CDATA[return variable name of action list]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[Username if URL is protected.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="url">
							<help><![CDATA[Required when action = 'update'. The URL to be executed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="starttime">
							<help><![CDATA[Required when creating tasks with action = 'update'. Enter a value in seconds. The time when 
	scheduling of the task starts.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="requesttimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Customizes the requestTimeOut for the task operation. Can be used to extend the default timeout 
		for operations that require more time to execute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the server from which the task is being scheduled. Default is 80. When used 
		with resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically resolved 
		to preserve links in the retrieved document.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="operation">
							<help><![CDATA[The type of operation the scheduler performs when executing this task.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="serverpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[allow you to access filesystem, also when access is denied for your context]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the proxy server from which the task is being requested. Default is 80. When 
		used with resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically 
		resolved to preserve links in the retrieved document.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="readonly">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enddate">
							<help><![CDATA[The date when the scheduled task ends.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="path">
							<help><![CDATA[Required with publish ='Yes' The path location for the published file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="publish">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether the result should be saved to a file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name or IP address of a proxy server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hidden">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="resolveurl">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to resolve links in the result page to absolute references.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="task">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the task to delete, update, or run.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="interval">
							<help><![CDATA[Required when creating tasks with action = 'update'. Interval at which task should be scheduled. 
		Can be set in seconds or as Once, Daily, Weekly, and Monthly. The default interval is one hour. The 
		minimum interval is one minute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="paused">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[Required with publish ='Yes' A valid filename for the published file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startdate">
							<help><![CDATA[Required when action ='update'. The date when scheduling of the task should start.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="endtime">
							<help><![CDATA[The time when the scheduled task ends. Enter a value in seconds.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfform">
					<help><![CDATA[Builds a form with CFML custom control tags that provide more functionality than standard 
  HTML form input elements.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="target">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the window or window frame to which the form output is sent.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the page that executed when the form is submitted for processing.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="lang">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passthrough">
							<help><![CDATA[Used for HTML attributes that are not explicitly supported by cfform. If you specify an 
		attribute and value, they are passed to the HTML code that is generated for the cfinput tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="accept">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseover">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enablecab">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="class">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the form you are creating.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="preloader">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ondblclick">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeydown">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="codebase">
							<help><![CDATA[URL for a downloadable JRE plugin (for Internet exploroer only). Default is 
		/CFIDE/classes/cf-j2re-win.cab.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="skin">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onsubmit">
							<help><![CDATA[JavaScript function to execute after other input validation returns. Use this attribute to 
		execute JavaScript for preprocessing data before the form is submitted]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="preservedata">
							<help><![CDATA[Optional. "Yes" or "No." Specifies whether to display the data that was entered into cfform 
		controls in the action page. "Yes" resets the value of the control to the value submitted when the 
		form is submitted to itself. This works as expected for the cftextinput and cfslider controls.
		This attribute can be used only if the form and action are on a single page, or if the action page has
		a form that contains controls with the same names as the corresponding controls on the form page.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseup">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="wmode">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scriptsrc">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="accessible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmousedown">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onclick">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeypress">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmousemove">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onreset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeyup">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="method">
							<help><![CDATA[other than post will ignored]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enctype">
							<help><![CDATA[The MIME type used to encode data sent by the POST method. The default value is application/x-www-form-urlencoded.
		It is recommended that you accept the default value. This attribute is included for compatibility with
		the HTML form tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="archive">
							<help><![CDATA[URL for a downloadable Java classes for controls.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onload">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dir">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="acceptcharset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfinterface">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="displayname">
							<help><![CDATA[A value to be displayed when using introspection to show a descriptive name for the interface.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="extends">
							<help><![CDATA[A comma-delimited list of one or more interfaces that this interface extends. 
			Any CFC that implements an interface must also implement all the functions in the interfaces specified by this property.
If an interface extends another interface, and the child interface specifies a function with the same name as one in the parent interface, 
both functions must have the same attributes; otherwise 
 generates an error.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hint">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfwddx">
					<help><![CDATA[Serializes and de-serializes CFML data structures to the XML-based WDDX format. 
  Generates JavaScript statements to instantiate JavaScript objects equivalent to the contents of a 
  WDDX packet or some CFML data structures.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="output">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the variable to hold the output of the operation. This attribute is required for 
		action = 'WDDX2CFML'. For all other actions, if this attribute is not provided, the result of the 
		WDDX processing is outputted in the HTML stream.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="input">
							<help><![CDATA[The value to be processed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="xmlconform">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the action taken by the cfwddx tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="validate">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="usetimezoneinfo">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates whether to output time-zone information when serializing CFML to WDDX. If time-zone 
		information is taken into account, the hour-minute offset, as represented in the ISO8601 format, is 
		calculated in the date-time output. If time-zone information is not taken into account, the local 
		time is output. The default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="toplevelvariable">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the top-level JavaScript object created by the deserialization process. The object 
		created is an instance of the WddxRecordset object, explained in WddxRecordset Object.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfloginuser">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[The Password of the User]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The Name of the User]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="roles">
							<help><![CDATA[The Roles of the User]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfhttpparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Required for cfhttp POST operations, cfhttpparam is used to specify the parameters necessary to 
	 build a cfhttp POST.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="mimetype">
							<help><![CDATA[Applies to File type; invalid for all other types. Specifies the MIME media type of the file contents. The content type can include an identifier for the character encoding of the file; for example, text/html; charset=ISO-8859-1 indicates that the file is HTML text in the ISO Latin-1 character encoding.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A variable name for the data being passed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[Required for type = "File".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[The transaction type.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the value of the URL, FormField, Cookie, File, or CGI variable being passed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="encoded">
							<help><![CDATA[Applies to FormField and CGI types; ignored for all other types. Specifies whether to URLEncode the form field or header.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfargument">
					<help><![CDATA[Allows subtag data to be saved with the base tag. Applies only to custom tags.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the argument]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="default">
							<help><![CDATA[default value of the argument]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="displayname">
							<help><![CDATA[name to display (only used by components)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[the type of the argumentany (array, binary, boolean, date, guid, numeric, query, string, struct, uuid)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passby">
							<help><![CDATA[should the argument passed as reference (default) or as a value]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="required">
							<help><![CDATA[is argument required or not]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hint">
							<help><![CDATA[hint to the argument (only used by components)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfformitem">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bind">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfvideoplayerparam">
					<help><![CDATA[play a video]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="video">
							<help><![CDATA[Path to the FLV file. Can be a URL or local file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="image">
							<help><![CDATA[This is just an alias for the attribute preview.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="author">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the author.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="flash">
							<help><![CDATA[Path to the SWF file. Can be a URL or local file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="index">
							<help><![CDATA[Layer in which the video is displayed. (not supported yet)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="preview">
							<help><![CDATA[Path to a preview image for playlist and main video display. Can be URL or local file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="link">
							<help><![CDATA[Displays a tiny image and allows linking to any target. (HTML link, Ajax etc.)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help><![CDATA[Title of the video. Displayed in the playlist as the title.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="show">
							<help><![CDATA[Defines whether the video should be displayed or not.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcalendar">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="endrange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="monthnames">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="disabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onblur">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="firstdayofweek">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="daynames">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mask">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="selecteddate">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onchange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onfocus">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftextinput">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you place a single-line text entry box in a cfform. The tag also gives you control over 
  font characteristics.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="bgcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Background color of the control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onerror">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of a JavaScript function to execute in the event of a failed validation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="italic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes for italicized text, No for normal text. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Vertical spacing of the control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onvalidate">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a JavaScript function used to validate user input. The form object, input object, 
	and input object value are passed to the routine, which should return TRUE if validation succeeds and 
	FALSE otherwise. When used, the validate attribute is ignored.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="required">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. If Yes, the user must enter or change text. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="message">
							<help><![CDATA[Message text to display if validation fails.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="range">
							<help><![CDATA[Minimum value, maximum value range, separated by a comma. Valid only for numeric data.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Horizontal spacing of the control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="validate">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="font">
							<help><![CDATA[Font name for text.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="size">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of characters displayed before horizontal scroll bar displays.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[Height value of the control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes for boldface text, No for medium text. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[Width value of the control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Initial value that displays in the text control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="notsupported">
							<help><![CDATA[The text to display if the page containing a Java applet-based 
	cfform control is opened by a browser that does not support Java or has Java support disabled.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxlength">
							<help><![CDATA[The maximum length of text entered.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Font size for text.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="textcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Text color for the control. See bgColor for color options.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the cftextinput control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfimport">
					<help><![CDATA[To import a JSP Taglibrary or a CFML Custom Tag Directory]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="taglib">
							<help><![CDATA[Path to a custom tag libraray or a jsp tld]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="prefix">
							<help><![CDATA[Prefix by which to access the imported custom CFML tags JSP tags. 

If you import a CFML custom tag directory and specify an empty value, "", for this attribute, you can call the custom tags without using a prefix. You must specify and use a prefix for a JSP tag library.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="path">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfoutput">
					<help><![CDATA[Displays the results of a database query or other operation. To nest cfoutput tags, see the "Usage" section.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="groupcasesensitive">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to group by case. The default value is YES; case is considered while 
		grouping. If the query attribute specifies a query object that was generated by a case-insensitive 
		SQL query, set the groupCaseSensitive attribute to NO to keep the recordset intact.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of rows to display in the output section.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the row from which to start output.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the cfquery from which to draw data for the output section.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="group">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the query column to use when you group sets of records together. Use this attribute 
		if you have retrieved a record set ordered on a certain query column. For example, if a record set is 
		ordered according to "CustomerID" in the cfquery tag, you can group the output on "CustomerID." The 
		group attribute, which is case sensitive, eliminates adjacent duplicates when the data is sorted by 
		the specified field. See the groupCaseSensitive attribute for information about specifying a case i
		nsensitive grouping.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfscript">
					<help><![CDATA[Encloses a code segment containing cfscript.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="language">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdocumentitem">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfmail">
					<help><![CDATA[Sends e-mail messages by an SMTP server.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="wraptext">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum line length, in characters of the mail text. If a line has more than the specified number of characters, replaces the last white space character, such as a tab or space, preceding the specified position with a line break. If there are no white space characters, inserts a line break at the specified position. A common value for this attribute is 72.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid username.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[A password to send to SMTP servers that require authentication. Requires a username attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="to">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the e-mail message recipient.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="spoolenable">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help><![CDATA[Character encoding of the mail message]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies extended type attributes for the message.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[A user name to send to SMTP servers that require authentication. Requires a password attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the cfquery from which to draw data for message(s) to send. Specify this 
		attribute to send more than one mail message, or to send the results of a query within a message.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="subject">
							<help><![CDATA[The subject of the mail message. This field may be driven dynamically on 
		a message-by-message basis]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="group">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the query column to use when you group sets of records together to send as an e-mail 
		message. For example, if you send a set of billing statements to customers, you might group on 
		"Customer_ID." The group attribute, which is case sensitive, eliminates adjacent duplicates when the 
		data is sorted by the specified field. See the Usage section for exceptions.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[The number of seconds to wait before timing out the connection to the SMTP server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="groupcasesensitive">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to group with regard to case or not. The default value is YES; 
		case is considered while grouping. If the query attribute specifies a query object that was generated 
		by a case-insensitive SQL query, set the groupCaseSensitive attribute to NO to keep the recordset 
		intact.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[The TCP/IP port on which the SMTP server listens for requests. This is normally 25.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ssl">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the proxy server from which the object is requested. Default is 80. When 
	used with resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically 
	resolved to preserve links in the retrieved document.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tls">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid password.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="secure">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for ssl]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cc">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates addresses to copy the e-mail message to; "cc" stands for "carbon copy."]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="server">
							<help><![CDATA[The address of the SMTP server to use for sending messages. If no server is specified, the 
		server name specified in the Railo Administrator is used.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="from">
							<help><![CDATA[The sender of the e-mail message.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the row in the query to start from.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="replyto">
							<help><![CDATA[Address(es) to which the recipient is directed to send replies.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name or IP address of a proxy server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of e-mail messages to send.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bcc">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates addresses to copy the e-mail message to, without listing them in the message header. 
		"bcc" stands for "blind carbon copy."]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mimeattach">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the path of the file to be attached to the e-mail message. An attached file 
		is MIME-encoded.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="failto">
							<help><![CDATA[Address to which mailing systems should send delivery failure notifications. Sets the mail envelope reverse-path value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="usessl">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for ssl]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="usetls">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for tls]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="priority">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="starttls">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for tls]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mailerid">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies a mailer ID to be passed in the X-Mailer SMTP header, which identifies the mailer 
		application.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="remove">
							<help><![CDATA[remove all attachments from filesystem after the mail is sucessful sended]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdiv">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfexecute">
					<help><![CDATA[Enables developers to execute a process on a server computer.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="outputfile">
							<help><![CDATA[The file to which to direct the output of the program. If not specified, the output is 
		displayed on the page from which it was called.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="terminateontimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[terminate execution of proccess when timeout occur]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[Variable in which to put program output. 
				If no outputfile or variable attribute is specified, 
				output is displayed on page from which it was called.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The full pathname of the application to execute.
		Note: On Windows, you must specify the extension as part of the application's name. For example, 
		myapp.exe,]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates how long, in seconds, the executing thread waits for the spawned process. 
		A timeout of 0 is equivalent to the non-blocking mode of executing. A very high timeout value is 
		equivalent to a blocking mode of execution. The default is 0; therefore, the thread spawns 
		a process and returns without waiting for the process to terminate.If no output file is specified, 
		and the timeout value is 0, the program output is discarded.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="arguments">
							<help><![CDATA[Command-line arguments passed to the application.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfinclude">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you embed references to pages in CFML. You can embed cfinclude tags recursively. 
  For an additional method of encapsulating CFML]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="template">
							<help><![CDATA[A logical path to an existing page.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfslider">
					<help><![CDATA[Used inside cfform, cfslider lets you place a slider control in a CFML form. A slider 
  control is like a sliding volume control. The slider groove is the area over which the slider moves.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="bgcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Background color of slider label. See textColor for color options.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onerror">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a valid JavaScript function to execute in the event of a failed validation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tickmarklabels">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vertical">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes renders the slider in the browser vertically. No renders the slider horizontally.
	This is the default.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="refreshlabel">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. If Yes, the label is not refreshed when the slider is moved. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tickmarkminor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="italic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes for italicized label text, No for normal text. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Vertical margin spacing above and below slider control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="label">
							<help><![CDATA[A label that displays with the slider control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onvalidate">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a valid JavaScript function used to validate user input; in this case, 
		a change to the default slider value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="message">
							<help><![CDATA[Message text to appear if validation fails.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="range">
							<help><![CDATA[The values of the left and right slider range. The slider value displays as the slider is moved. 
    Separate values by a comma.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="lookandfeel">
							<help><![CDATA[A stylistic choice for the slider.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="font">
							<help><![CDATA[Font name for label text.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Horizontal margin spacing to the left and right of slider control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[Height of the slider control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bold">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter Yes for bold label text, No for medium text. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[Width of the slider control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tickmarkimages">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[The starting slider setting. Must be within the values specified in range. Defaults to the 
		minimum value specified in range.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="notsupported">
							<help><![CDATA[The text to display if a page containing a Java applet-based cfform control is opened by a 
		browser that does not support Java or has Java support disabled.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tickmarkmajor">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes to render major tickmarks in the slider scale. No for no major tickmarks. Default is No. 
    Major tick marks are the marks that appear at the intervals specified by the Scale attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Font size for label text measured in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="textcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Slider label text color. Valid entries are: black, magenta, 
	cyan, orange, darkgray, pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scale">
							<help><![CDATA[Unsigned integer. Defines the slider scale within the value of range.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the cfslider control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfvideoplayer">
					<help><![CDATA[play a video]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="bgcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[background color]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="thumbnails">
							<help><![CDATA[using Thumbnails in playlist or not (alias for playlistThumbnails)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="foreground">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for fgcolor]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="thumbs">
							<help><![CDATA[using Thumbnails in playlist or not (alias for playlistThumbnails)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showplay">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showtimeline">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="download">
							<help><![CDATA[Set this to true to show a download button in the player controlbar]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="linkfromdisplay">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="playlistthumbnails">
							<help><![CDATA[using Thumbnails in playlist or not]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="group">
							<help><![CDATA[if multiple video are defined, you have to define if this videos should be break a part or played as a single video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="lightcolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="foregroundcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for fgcolor]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showpause">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overstretch">
							<help><![CDATA[Sets how to stretch images/movies to make them fit the display. Set this to true to stretch them proportionally to fill the display, fit to stretch them disproportionally and none to keep original dimensions]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="screencolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passthrough">
							<help><![CDATA[attribute to pass natively vales to player]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="debug">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="preview">
							<help><![CDATA[set this to the path of a preview image.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="linktarget">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fgcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[foreground color]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="playlistsize">
							<help><![CDATA[size of the playlist, if playlist is right of display this is the width otherwise the height]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="background">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for bgcolor]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="video">
							<help><![CDATA[path to Movie File (flv/mp4)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="playlist">
							<help><![CDATA[define if and where the playlist will be displayed]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="allowfullscreen">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="autostart">
							<help><![CDATA[Set this to true in the player to automatically start playing when the page loads]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="target">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="backgroundcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for bgcolor]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfprocessingdirective">
					<help><![CDATA[Suppresses extra white space and other output, produced by CFML within the tag's scope.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="suppresswhitespace">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to suppress the white space and other output generated by the 
		CFML tags within the cfprocessingdirective block.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pageencoding">
							<help><![CDATA[A string literal; the character encoding to use to read the page. The value may be enclosed in single or double quotation marks, or none.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="executionlog">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to write execution log or not.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftry">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with one or more cfcatch tags, the cftry tag lets you catch and process exceptions in 
  CFML pages. Exceptions include events that disrupt the normal flow of instructions in a 
  CFML page, such as failed database operations, missing include files, and developer-specified 
  events.]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfexit">
					<help><![CDATA[Used to: Abort the processing of the currently executing CFML custom tag, exit the template 
	within the currently executing CFML custom tag and reexecute a section of code within the currently
	executing CFML custom tag]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="method">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdocumentsection">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="src">
							<help><![CDATA[define a url or or a relative path on the local system to a file that should be transfered to a pdf]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="margintop">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Bookmark name for the section]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="srcfile">
							<help><![CDATA[define a absolute path to a file that should be transfered to a pdf]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="useragent">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to put in the HTTP User-Agent request header field. Used to identify the request client software.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="marginbottom">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="marginright">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mimetype">
							<help><![CDATA[mimetype of the source (when attribute src or srcfile are defined)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="authpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[Password sent to the target URL for Basic Authentication. Combined with username to form a base64 encoded string that is passed in the Authenticate header. Does not provide support for Integrated Windows, NTLM, or Kerebos authentication.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="marginleft">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="authuser">
							<help><![CDATA[User name sent to the target URL for Basic Authentication. Combined with password to form a base64 encoded string that is passed in the Authenticate header. Does not provide support for Integrated Windows, NTLM, or Kerebos authentication.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfobjectcache">
					<help><![CDATA[Flushes the query cache]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[name for variables for action size]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filterignorecase">
							<help><![CDATA[filter for the elements to delete]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filter">
							<help><![CDATA[filter for the elements to delete]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Clears queries from the cache in the Application scope.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfmap">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfzipparam">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="entrypath">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filter">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="recurse">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="content">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="prefix">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfsearch">
					<help><![CDATA[Executes searches against data indexed]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="previouscriteria">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the search query.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="category">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="contexthighlightend">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="status">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="language">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of entries for index queries. If omitted, all rows are returned.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="contextpassages">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="collection">
							<help><![CDATA[The logical collection name that is the target of the search operation or an external collection 
		with fully qualified path.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="contextbytes">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="suggestions">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="external">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the criteria type for the search.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="criteria">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the criteria for the search following the syntactic rules specified by type.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="contexthighlightbegin">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the first row number to be retrieved. Default is 1.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="categorytree">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfgraphdata">
					<help><![CDATA[Specifies a data point to be displayed by a cfgraph tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="color">
							<help><![CDATA[The color to use when graphing the data point. The default is to use the values from the cfgraph
		tag colorlist attribute or the built-in default list of colors. Line graphs ignore this attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="url">
							<help><![CDATA[A URL to load when the user clicks the data point. This attribute works with Pie, Bar, and 
		HorizontalBar charts. This attribute has an effect only if the graph is in Flash file format.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="item">
							<help><![CDATA[The item label for the data point. The item labels appear on the horizontal axis of Line and 
		Bar charts, the vertical axis of Horizontal Bar charts, and in the legend of Pie charts.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Value to be represented by the data point.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdbinfo">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you retrieve information about a data source, including details about the database, tables, queries, procedures, foreign keys, indexes, and version information about the database, driver, and JDBC. This tag supports only JDBC drivers, and does not support ODBC-based drivers, including the Microsoft Access driver.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[Datasource to use to connect to the database.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="procedure">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the procedure from which you retrieve information.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name to use to refer to the result.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbname">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the database]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[User name to connect to the database.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pattern">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies a filter to retrieve information about specific tables, columns, or stored procedures]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of information to get]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[Password to connect to the database.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="table">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the table from which you retrieve information.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfadmin">
					<help><![CDATA[Tag for the railo web/server administrator]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcontent">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines the MIME type returned by the current page. Optionally, lets you specify the name of a file
  to be returned with the page.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="range">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes allows download ranges, no forbids download range, default let it open for client.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[the variable name to the content to output as binary]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the file being retrieved]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Defines the File/ MIME content type returned by the current page.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="deletefile">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes deletes the file after the download operation. Defaults to No. 
	This attribute applies only if you specify a file with the file attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="reset">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes discards output that precedes the call to cfcontent. No preserves the output that precedes the call. Defaults to Yes. The reset 
		and file attributes are mutually exclusive. If you specify a file, the reset attribute has no effect.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="content">
							<help><![CDATA[the content to output as binary]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcol">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines table column header, width, alignment, and text. Used only inside a cftable.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[The width of the column in characters (the default is 20). If the length of the data displayed exceeds the width value, 
		the data is truncated to fit.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="text">
							<help><![CDATA[Double-quote delimited text that determines what displays in the column. The rules for the text
		attribute are identical to the rules for cfoutput sections; it can consist of a combination of 
		literal text, HTML tags, and query record set field references. You can embed hyperlinks, image 
		references, and input controls in columns.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="header">
							<help><![CDATA[The text for the column's header.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help><![CDATA[Column alignment, Left, Right, or Center.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cffile">
					<help><![CDATA[Handles all interactions with files. The attributes you use with cffile depend on the value of the action attribute. 
 For example, if the action = "write", use the attributes associated with writing a text file.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="nameconflict">
							<help><![CDATA[Action to take if filename is the same as that of a file in the directory.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help><![CDATA[Absolute pathname of file on web server. 
On Windows, use backward slashes; on UNIX, use forward slashes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fixnewline">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="output">
							<help><![CDATA[Content of the file to be created.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[Absolute pathname of file on web server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help><![CDATA[Character set name for the file contents.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="accept">
							<help><![CDATA[Limits the MIME types to accept. Comma-delimited list. For example, to permit JPG and Microsoft Word file uploads:
accept = "image/jpg, application/msword"
The browser uses file extension to determine file type.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of variable to contain contents of text file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of file manipulation that the tag performs.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="serverpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[allow you to access filesystem, also when access is denied for your context]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="addnewline">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes: appends newline character to text written to file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="attributes">
							<help><![CDATA[One attribute (Windows) or a comma-delimited list of attributes (other platforms) to set on the file. 
If omitted, the file's attributes are maintained.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mode">
							<help><![CDATA[Applies only to Solaris and HP-UX. Permissions. Octal values of UNIX chmod command. Assigned to owner, group, and other, respectively.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filefield">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of form field used to select the file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="destination">
							<help><![CDATA[Absolute pathname of directory or file on web server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="acl">
							<help><![CDATA[only used for S3 Resources]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the result value (default:cffile)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfinvoke">
					<help><![CDATA[Invokes component methods from within a page or component. 
			You use this tag to reference a WSDL file and consume a web service from within a block of CFML code.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="method">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="serviceport">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="webservice">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returnvariable">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="component">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcase">
					<help><![CDATA[Handle one case of a cfswicth]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[One or more constant values that cfswitch compares to the specified expression case-insensitive comparison. 
		If a value matches the expression, cfswitch executes the code between the cfcase start and end tags.
		Separate multiple values with a comma or other delimiter, as specified in the delimiters parameter. 
		Duplicate value attributes are not allowed and causes a runtime error.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiters">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the character that separates multiple entries in a list of values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfsilent">
					<help><![CDATA[Suppresses all output that is produced by the CFML within the tag's scope.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="bufferoutput">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfldap">
					<help><![CDATA[Provides an interface to LDAP Lightweight Directory Access Protocol 
  directory servers like the Netscape Directory Server.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[used when username is defined]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scope">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the scope of the search from the entry specified in the Start attribute 
		for action = "Query".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sortcontrol">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies how to sort query results.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="separator">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the character that cfldap uses to separate attribute values in multi-value attributes. This character is used by the query, add, and modify action attributes, and 
		by cfldap to output multi-value attributes. The default character is the comma (,).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If no user name is specified, the LDAP connection is anonymous.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="start">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the distinguished name of the entry to be used to start the search.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rebind">
							<help><![CDATA[If you set rebind to Yes, cfldap attempts to rebind the referral callback and reissue the query 
		by the referred address using the original credentials. The default is No, which means referred 
		connections are anonymous.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="attributes">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum amount of time, in seconds, to wait for LDAP processing. Defaults to 
		60 seconds.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[Port defaults to the standard LDAP port, 389.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filter">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returnasbinary">
							<help><![CDATA[A comma-delimited list of columns that are to be returned as binary values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="modifytype">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates whether to add, delete, or replace an attribute in a multi-value list of attributes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="secure">
							<help><![CDATA[The type of security to use]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="server">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name "biff.upperlip.com" or IP address "192.1.2.225" of the LDAP server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dn">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the distinguished name for update actions.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Used in conjunction with action = "Query". Specifies the first row of the LDAP query to insert 
		into the query. The default is 1.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the LDAP action.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filterfile">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the name of a filter file and of the stanza tag within the file that contains the 
		LDAP filter string specification. You can specify an absolute pathname or a simple filename to identify 
		the file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of entries for LDAP queries.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sort">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates the attribute or attributes by which to sort query results. Use a comma to separate attributes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiter">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the character that cfldap uses to separate multiple attribute name/value pairs when more than one attribute is specified in the attribute attribute or the attribute that you want to use has the default delimiter character, which is the semicolon (;), such as mgrpmsgrejecttext;lang-en. The delimiter character is used by the query, add, and 
		modify action attributes, and is used by cfldap to output multi-value attributes]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="referral">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of hops allowed in a referral. A value of 0 disables referred addresses for LDAP; no data is returned.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name you assign to the LDAP query.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcache">
					<help><![CDATA[Speeds up page rendering when dynamic content does not have to be retrieved each time a user accesses
  the page. To accomplish this, cfcache creates temporary files that contain the static HTML returned from
  a page. You can use cfcache for simple URLs and URLs that contain URL parameters.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="directory">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[When required for basic authentication, a valid password.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[When required for basic authentication, a valid username.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachedirectory">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="throwonerror">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="metadata">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="protocol">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the protocol used to create pages from cache. Either http:// or https://. The default
		is http://.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timespan">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachename">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="expireurl">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="idletime">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="key">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfstoredproc">
					<help><![CDATA[Executes stored procedures by an ODBC or native connection to a server database. It specifies database connection 
  information and identifies the stored procedure.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of an ODBC or native data source that points to the database that contains the stored 
		procedure.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="procedure">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the stored procedure on the database server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="debug">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Specifies whether debug info will be listed on each statement. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachename">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, username overrides the username value specified in the data source setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachedwithin">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachedafter">
							<help><![CDATA[This is the age of which the query data can be]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="blockfactor">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of rows to fetch at a time from the server. The range is 1 
		which is the default to 100. The ODBC driver may dynamically reduce the block factor at runtime.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returncode">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Specifies whether the tag populates cfstoredproc.statusCode with the status code 
	returned by the stored procedure. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[timeout for the stored procedure.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, password overrides the password value specified in the data source setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies a name for the structure in which cfstoredproc returns the statusCode and ExecutionTime variables.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfupdate">
					<help><![CDATA[Updates existing records in data sources.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="tableowner">
							<help><![CDATA[For data sources that support table ownership, for example, SQL Server, Oracle, and Sybase 
		SQL Anywhere, use this field to specify the owner of the table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the data source that contains a table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, password overrides the password value specified in the ODBC setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tablename">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the table you want to update.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tablequalifier">
							<help><![CDATA[For data sources that support table qualifiers, use this field to specify the qualifier for the 
		table. The purpose of table qualifiers varies across drivers. For SQL Server and Oracle, the qualifier 
		refers to the name of the database that contains the table. For the Intersolv dBase driver, the 
		qualifier refers to the directory where the DBF files are located.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="formfields">
							<help><![CDATA[A comma-separated list of form fields to update. If this attribute is not specified, all fields 
		in the form are included in the operation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, username overrides the username value specified in the ODBC setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfinsert">
					<help><![CDATA[Inserts records in data sources.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="tableowner">
							<help><![CDATA[For data sources that support table ownership such as SQL Server, Oracle, and Sybase SQL 
	Anywhere, use this field to specify the owner of the table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the data source that contains your table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, password overrides the password value specified in the ODBC setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tablename">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the table you want the form fields inserted in.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tablequalifier">
							<help><![CDATA[For data sources that support table qualifiers, use this field to specify the qualifier for the 
	table. The purpose of table qualifiers varies across drivers. For SQL Server and Oracle, the qualifier 
	refers to the name of the database that contains the table. For the Intersolv dBase driver, the 
	qualifier refers to the directory where the DBF files are located.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="formfields">
							<help><![CDATA[A comma-separated list of form fields to insert. If this attribute is not specified, all 
	fields in the form are included in the operation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, username overrides the username value specified in the ODBC setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfftp">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets users implement File Transfer Protocol (FTP) operations.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="directory">
							<help><![CDATA[remote directory to list]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid username.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[The Password for the connection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="failifexists">
							<help><![CDATA[throw a error if local file already exist or overwrite it]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[The Username for the connection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="stoponerror">
							<help><![CDATA[define if execution halt on error or not]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="transfermode">
							<help><![CDATA[ascci, binary or auto mode]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[timeout for the connection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[server port of the connection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="remotefile">
							<help><![CDATA[File on the Server]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the result value (default:cfftp)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="connection">
							<help><![CDATA[the name for the connection, used to cache the connection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="retrycount">
							<help><![CDATA[retry count]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the proxy server from which the object is requested. Default is 80. When 
	used with resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically 
	resolved to preserve links in the retrieved document.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="asciiextensionlist">
							<help><![CDATA[Delimited list of file extensions that force ASCII transfer mode, if transferMode = "auto".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid password.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="existing">
							<help><![CDATA[source or existing file or directory to rename]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="server">
							<help><![CDATA[The Server to connect]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="new">
							<help><![CDATA[new name for file or directory]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[the action that should be execute]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name or IP address of a proxy server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passive">
							<help><![CDATA[enable passive mode]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="localfile">
							<help><![CDATA[File on the current machine]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="item">
							<help><![CDATA[item on the server]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[name of the query for list directory]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfset">
					<help><![CDATA[Define a CFML variable. If the variable exists, cfset resets it to the specified value.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="noname">
							<help><![CDATA[Content of the tag set]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cffunction">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines table column header, width, alignment, and text. Used only inside a cftable.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A string; a component method that is used within the cfcomponent tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="output">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute is used only for a component.

yes: the function is processed as if it were within a cfoutput tag 
no: the function is processed as if it were within a cfsilent tag]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returntype">
							<help><![CDATA[String; a type name; data type of the function return value]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="access">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute is used only for a component.
The client security context from which the method can be invoked]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hint">
							<help><![CDATA[Hint of the Function]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="displayname">
							<help><![CDATA[Display Name of the Function]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="roles">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute is used only for a component. If this attribute is omitted, all roles can invoke the method.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="verifyclient">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="abstract">
							<help><![CDATA[is the function abstract or not, abstract functions are only allowed inside interface or component tags]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returnformat">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="securejson">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="description">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfvideo">
					<help><![CDATA[play a video]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="buffersize">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="comment">
							<help><![CDATA[comment meta data of the destinatin video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="copyright">
							<help><![CDATA[copyright meta data of the destinatin video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fps">
							<help><![CDATA[how many frames are used per second]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="profile">
							<help><![CDATA[standart profile definition (declared in video.xml)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="author">
							<help><![CDATA[author meta data of the destinatin video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="start">
							<help><![CDATA[offset of destination video based on source, you can defines frames (10f) or time (1145ms,3.123s)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="videobitratemin">
							<help><![CDATA[minimal video bitrate of variable bitrate, default same as input or part of defined quality  (example: 10kbps, 10mbps, 10bps)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="nameconflict">
							<help><![CDATA[Action to take if filename is the same as that of a file in the directory. (error,skip,overwrite,makeunique)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="videobitrate">
							<help><![CDATA[video bitrate, default same as input or part of defined quality (example: 10kbps, 10mbps, 10bps)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="videobitratemax">
							<help><![CDATA[maximal video bitrate of variable bitrate, default same as input or part of defined quality (example: 10kbps, 10mbps, 10bps)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source2">
							<help><![CDATA["right" source video to read in for concatination]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source1">
							<help><![CDATA["left" source video to read in for concatination]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[name of struct that hold action info (default:cfvideo)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="quality">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for profile]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="audiobitrate">
							<help><![CDATA[audio bitrate, default same as input or part of defined quality (example: 10kbps, 10mbps, 10bps)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="videocodec">
							<help><![CDATA[force video codec]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="execution">
							<help><![CDATA[values can be "quality" or "performance"]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[height of destination video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="debug">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help><![CDATA[source video to read in]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[width of destination video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="destination">
							<help><![CDATA[directory of the destination video to create]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of video manipulation that the tag performs. provided actions are [info,convert,cutimage,concat]]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="max">
							<help><![CDATA[maximal length of destination video, you can defines max frame (10f) or max time (1145ms,3.123s)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="aspectratio">
							<help><![CDATA[aspect ratio (16:9,4:3)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="framerate">
							<help><![CDATA[how many frames are used per second (alias for fps)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="audiosamplerate">
							<help><![CDATA[audio sampling rate, default same as input or part of defined quality]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="videobitratetolerance">
							<help><![CDATA[video bitrate tolerance of variable bitrate, default same as input or part of defined quality (example: 10kbps, 10mbps, 10bps)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="audiocodec">
							<help><![CDATA[force audio codec]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="data">
							<help><![CDATA[for internal use only]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help><![CDATA[title meta data of the destinatin video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[name of the destination video]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfjavascript">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfmailpart">
					<help><![CDATA[Specifies one part of a multipart e-mail message. Can only be used in the cfmail tag. You can use more than one cfmailpart tag within a cfmail tag]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[The MIME media type of the part]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="wraptext">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum line length, in characters of the mail text]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help><![CDATA[The character encoding in which the part text is encoded]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfif">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with cfelse and cfelseif, cfif lets you create simple and compound conditional statements 
  in CFML. The value in the cfif tag can be any expression.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="contition">
							<help><![CDATA[Contition o the expression]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cffinally">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfgridupdate">
					<help><![CDATA[Used in a cfgrid, cfgridupdate allows you to perform updates to data sources directly from edited 
  grid data. The cfgridupdate tag provides a direct interface with your data source. 
  The cfgridupdate tag applies delete row actions first, then INSERT row actions, and then UPDATE row 
  actions. If an error is encountered, row processing stops.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the data source for the update action.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="grid">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the cfgrid form element that is the source for the update action.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbname">
							<help><![CDATA[The database name (Sybase System 11 driver and SQLOLEDB provider only). If specified, 
	dbName overrides the default database specified in the data source.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tablequalifier">
							<help><![CDATA[For data sources that support table qualifiers, use this field to specify the qualifier for the 
	table. The purpose of table qualifiers varies across drivers. For SQL Server and Oracle, the qualifier
	refers to the name of the database that contains the table. For the Intersolv dBase driver, the qualifier 
	refers to the directory where the DBF files are located.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="providerdsn">
							<help><![CDATA[Data source name for the COM provider (OLE-DB only).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, username overrides the username value specified in the ODBC setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tablename">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the table to update.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="keyonly">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes specifies that in the update action, the WHERE criteria is confined to the key 
	values. No specifies that in addition to the key values, the original values of any changed fields 
	are included in the WHERE criteria. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbserver">
							<help><![CDATA[For native database drivers and the SQLOLEDB provider, specifies the name of the database 
	server computer. If specified, dbServer overrides the server specified in the data source.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="connectstring">
							<help><![CDATA[The contents of a connection string to send to the ODBC server. When connecting to a data 
	source defined in the Railo Administrator, you can use this attribute to specify additional 
	connection details or to override connection information specified in the Administrator. If you are 
	dynamically connecting to a datasource by specifying dbType = "dynamic", the connection string must 
	specify all required ODBC connection attributes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="provider">
							<help><![CDATA[COM provider (OLE-DB only).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tableowner">
							<help><![CDATA[For data sources that support table ownership (such as SQL Server, Oracle, and Sybase SQL 
	Anywhere), use this field to specify the owner of the table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, password overrides the password value specified in the ODBC setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbtype">
							<help><![CDATA[The database driver type]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfquery">
					<help><![CDATA[Passes SQL statements to a data source. Not limited to queries.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, password overrides the password value specified in the data source setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="unique">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies if the object parameter is unique, used only for dbtype=orm or hql]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="blockfactor">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of rows to fetch at a time from the server. The range is 1, 
		default to 100. This parameter applies to ORACLE native database drivers and to ODBC drivers. 
		Certain ODBC drivers may dynamically reduce the block factor at runtime.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If specified, username overrides the username value specified in the data source setup.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbserver">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="providerdsn">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datasource">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the data source from which this query should retrieve data.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachedwithin">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ormoptions">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[The maximum number of milliseconds for the query to execute before returning an error 
		indicating that the query has timed-out. This attribute is not supported by most ODBC drivers. 
		timeout is supported by the SQL Server 6.x or above driver. The minimum and maximum allowable values 
		vary, depending on the driver.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="debug">
							<help><![CDATA[Used for debugging queries. Specifying this attribute causes the SQL statement submitted to the 
		data source and the number of records returned from the query to be returned.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="returntype">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbname">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="psq">
							<help><![CDATA[preserve single quote or not]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachedafter">
							<help><![CDATA[This is the age of which the query data can be]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cachename">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of rows to return in the record set.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="connectstring">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbtype">
							<help><![CDATA[The database driver type.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="provider">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name query. Must begin with a letter and may consist of letters, numbers, and the underscore 
		character, spaces are not allowed. The query name is used later in the page to reference the query's 
		record set.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdefaultcase">
					<help><![CDATA[Handles interactions with directories.]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdocument">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="mimetype">
							<help><![CDATA[mimetype of the source (when attribute src or srcfile are defined)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid username.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overwrite">
							<help><![CDATA[define if a existing file will be overwritten or not]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontembed">
							<help><![CDATA[define if fonts will embeded with the file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="orientation">
							<help><![CDATA[is the orientation landscape or portrait]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="userpassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pagetype">
							<help><![CDATA[defined the used format for the page (,legal,letter,A4,A5,B4,B5,B4-JIS,B5-JIS and custom)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="authuser">
							<help><![CDATA[User name sent to the target URL for Basic Authentication. Combined with password to form a base64 encoded string that is passed in the Authenticate header. Does not provide support for Integrated Windows, NTLM, or Kerebos authentication.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="src">
							<help><![CDATA[define a url or or a relative path on the local system to a file that should be transfered to a pdf]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bookmark">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether bookmarks are created in the document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ownerpassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="permissions">
							<help><![CDATA[define permissions for the file (AllowPrinting,AllowModifyContents,AllowCopy,AllowModifyAnnotations,AllowFillIn,AllowScreenReaders,AllowAssembly,AllowDegradedPrinting)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="backgroundvisible">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether the background prints when the user prints the document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="marginleft">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the proxy server from which the object is requested. Default is 80. When 
	used with resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically 
	resolved to preserve links in the retrieved document.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pageheight">
							<help><![CDATA[used when pagetype is custom]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="srcfile">
							<help><![CDATA[define a absolute path to a file that should be transfered to a pdf]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="unit">
							<help><![CDATA[set the unit for pageheight, pagewidth, and margin...]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid password.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="localurl">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to retrieve image files directly from the local drive]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="encryption">
							<help><![CDATA[define if the outputshould be encrypted and how deep]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="authpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[Password sent to the target URL for Basic Authentication. Combined with username to form a base64 encoded string that is passed in the Authenticate header. Does not provide support for Integrated Windows, NTLM, or Kerebos authentication.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyhost">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name or IP address of a proxy server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pagewidth">
							<help><![CDATA[used when pagetyp is custom]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="useragent">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to put in the HTTP User-Agent request header field. Used to identify the request client software.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filename">
							<help><![CDATA[name for output file, if not defined outputt will be written to response stream]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help><![CDATA[alias for proxyHost]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help><![CDATA[format of the created file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="marginbottom">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="margintop">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="saveasname">
							<help><![CDATA[(format="PDF" only) The filename that appears in the SaveAs dialog when a user saves a PDF file written to the browser.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="htmlbookmark">
							<help><![CDATA[if true it is possible to convert to outlines a list of named anchors (<a name="anchor_id">label</a>) 
				or a headings structure (<h1>...<h6>).
				Transforming of HTML hyperlinks to PDF hyperlinks (if not explicitely disabled). 
				Hyperlink jumps within the same document are supported as well]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="marginright">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scale">
							<help><![CDATA[define a scale factor as a percentage. this option is used to reduce the size of the HTML output so that it fits on that paper. define a number less than 100.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[name of a variable to store the ouptut in it]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftimer">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="label">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftrace">
					<help><![CDATA[Displays and logs debugging data about the state of an application at the time the cftrace tag executes. 
			Tracks runtime logic flow, variable values, and execution time. Displays output at the end of the request 
			or in the debugging section at the end of the request; or, in Dreamweaver MX and later, in the Server Debug 
			tab of the Results window.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="var">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="category">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="inline">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="text">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="abort">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfgridcolumn">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with cfgrid in a cfform, you use cfgridcolumn to specify column data in a cfgrid control. Font and alignment 
  attributes used in cfgridcolumn override any global font or alignment settings defined in cfgrid.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="bgcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Color value for the background of the grid column, or an expression you can use to manipulate grid 
		column background color. Valid color entries are: black, magenta, cyan, orange, darkgray, pink, gray, 
		white (default), lightgray, yellow.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="values">
							<help><![CDATA[Formats cells in the column as drop down list boxes. lets end users select an item in a drop 
		down list. Use the values attribute to specify the items you want to appear in the drop down list.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headeralign">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment for the column header text. Default is as specified by cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dataalign">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment for column data. Entries are: left, center, or right. Default is as specified 
		by cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuesdelimiter">
							<help><![CDATA[Character to use as a delimiter in the values and valuesDisplay attributes. Default 
		is "," (comma).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="italic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays all grid control text in italic. Default is as specified by the 
		corresponding attribute of cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hrefkey">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a query column when the grid uses a query. The column specified becomes the Key 
		regardless of the select mode for the grid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="font">
							<help><![CDATA[Font name to use for data in the column. Defaults is the font specified by cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="select">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes lets end users select a column in a grid control. When No, the column cannot 
		be edited, even if the cfgrid insert or delete attributes are enabled. The value of the select 
		attribute is ignored if the cfgrid selectMode attribute is set to Row or Browse.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays all grid control text in boldface. Default is as specified by the 
		corresponding attribute of cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[The width of the column, in pixels. Default is the width of the column head text.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headerfontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Font size to use for the column header, in pixels. Default is as specified by the 
		orresponding attribute of cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="display">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Use to hide columns. Default is Yes to display the column.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headertextcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Color value for the grid control column header text. Entries are: black (default), magenta, 
		cyan, orange, darkgray, pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="header">
							<help><![CDATA[Text for the column header. The value of header is used only when the cfgrid colHeaders 
		attribute is Yes (or omitted, since it defaults to Yes).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mask">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="href">
							<help><![CDATA[URL to associate with the grid item. You can specify a URL that is relative to the current page]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="numberformat">
							<help><![CDATA[The format for displaying numeric data in the grid. For information about mask characters, 
		see "numberFormat mask characters".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headerfont">
							<help><![CDATA[Font to use for the column header. Default is as specified by the corresponding attribute of 
		cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Font size for text in the column. Default is the font specified by cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headeritalic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays column header text in italic. Default is as specified by the 
		corresponding attribute of cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headerbold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays header text in boldface. Default is as specified by the 
		corresponding attribute of cfgrid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="textcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Color value for grid element text in the grid column, or an expression you can use to manipulate text 
		color in grid column elements. Valid color entries are: black (default), magenta, cyan, orange, 
		arkgray, pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="target">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the frame in which to open the link specified in href.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuesdisplay">
							<help><![CDATA[Used to map elements specified in the values attribute to a string of your choice to display 
		in the drop down list. Enter comma separated strings and/or numeric range(s).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the grid column element. If the grid uses a query, the column name must specify the 
		name of a query column.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcookie">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines cookie variables, including expiration and security options.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="expires">
							<help><![CDATA[Schedules the expiration of a cookie variable. Can be specified as a date (as in, 10/09/97), 
	number of days (as in, 10, 100), "Now", or "Never". Using Now effectively deletes the cookie from
	the client browser.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the cookie variable.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[The value assigned to the cookie variable.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="domain">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="secure">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Specifies that the variable must transmit securely. If the browser does not support
	Secure Socket Layer (SSL) security, the cookie is not sent.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="path">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcontinue">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfservlet">
					<help><![CDATA[This tag has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="debug">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="writeoutput">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="jrunproxy">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="code">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfauthenticate">
					<help><![CDATA[Authenticates a user, setting a security context for the application. 
			For more information, see the descriptions of IsAuthenticated and AuthenticatedContext.]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfsavecontent">
					<help><![CDATA[Saves the generated content inside the tag body in a variable.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="trim">
							<help><![CDATA[trim result]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the variable in which to save the generated content inside the tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcomponent">
					<help><![CDATA[Creates and defines a component object; encloses functionality that you build in CFML and enclose within cffunction tags. This tag contains one or more cffunction tags that define methods. Code within the body of this tag, other than cffunction tags, is executed when the component is instantiated.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether a CFC used for web services uses RPC-encoded style or document-literal style]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="output">
							<help><![CDATA[yes: permits component method output
				no: suppresses component method output]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="namespace">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="persistent">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="extends">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of parent component from which to inherit methods and properties.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hint">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="displayname">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="synchronized">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="wsdlfile">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="porttypename">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="display">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="serviceportname">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bindingname">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftree">
					<help><![CDATA[This Tag is not supported yet.
		Lets you put a tree control in a cfform. Validates user selections. Tree items are created with 
  cftreeitem tags inside the cftree tag block. You can use a CFML query to supply data to the tree.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="onerror">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a JavaScript function to execute in the event of a failed validation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onblur">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="italic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays tree control text in italic. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Vertical margin spacing above and below the tree control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onvalidate">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a valid JavaScript function used to validate user input. The form object, input 
	object, and input object value are passed to the specified routine, which should return true if 
	validation succeeds and false otherwise.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="completepath">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes passes the root level of the treename.path form variable when the cftree is submitted. If 
	omitted or No, the root level of this form variable is not included. You must set this attribute to 
	Yes for the preserveData attribute of cfform to work with the tree.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="required">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Whether user must select an item in the tree control. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="message">
							<help><![CDATA[Message text to appear if validation fails.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="appendkey">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. When used with href, Yes passes the CFTREEITEMKEY variable along with the value of 
	the selected tree item in the URL to the application page specified in the cfform action attribute. 
	The default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="lookandfeel">
							<help><![CDATA[Stylistic choice for the slider.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="font">
							<help><![CDATA[Font name to use for data in the tree control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[Height of the tree control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays tree control text in boldface. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[Width of the tree control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="border">
							<help><![CDATA[Places a border around the tree. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="notsupported">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to display if the page containing a Java applet-based cfform control is opened by a 
	browser that does not support Java or has Java support disabled.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onchange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hscroll">
							<help><![CDATA[Permits horizontal scrolling. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Font size for text in the tree control, in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vscroll">
							<help><![CDATA[Permits vertical scrolling. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onfocus">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiter">
							<help><![CDATA[The character used to separate elements in the form variable path.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the cftree control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Tests for a parameter's existence, tests its data type, and provides a default value if one 
  is not assigned.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="max">
							<help><![CDATA[define the biggest size of a numeric value, used for type range]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the parameter to test, such as Client.Email or Cookie.BackgroundColor. If 
		you omit the DEFAULT attribute, an error occurs if the specified parameter does not exist]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="default">
							<help><![CDATA[Default value to set the parameter to if it does not exist.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="min">
							<help><![CDATA[define the smallest size of a numeric value, used for type range]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[The type of parameter that is required. The default is 'any'.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pattern">
							<help><![CDATA[define a regular expression pattern, to check value against]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfzip">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="recurse">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filter">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="storepath">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="entrypath">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showdirectory">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="prefix">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overwrite">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="destination">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftable">
					<help><![CDATA[Builds a table in a CFML page. Use the cfcol tag to define table column and row 
  characteristics. The cftable tag renders data either as preformatted text, or, with the HTMLTable 
  attribute, as an HTML table. Use cftable to create tables if you don't want to write HTML table tag 
  code, or if your data can be well presented as preformatted text.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="border">
							<help><![CDATA[Adds a border to the table. Use only when you specify the HTMLTable attribute for the table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="headerlines">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of lines to use for the table header. The default is 2, which leaves one line between 
		the headers and the first row of the table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Maximum number of rows to display in the table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="htmltable">
							<help><![CDATA[Renders the table as an HTML 3.0 table.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the query row from which to start processing.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaders">
							<help><![CDATA[Displays headers for each column, as specified in the cfcol tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colspacing">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of spaces to insert between columns 'default is 2'.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the cfquery from which to draw data.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflogout">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfapplet">
					<help><![CDATA[Used in a cfform tag, cfapplet lets you reference custom Java applets that you have registered 
			using the Railo Administrator.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The form variable name for the applet.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[The width of the applet, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="appletsource">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the registered applet.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Space above and below applet, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="notsupported">
							<help><![CDATA[The text to display if a page containing a Java applet-based cfform control is opened by a browser that does not support Java or has Java support disabled.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="paramn">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a registered parameter for the applet.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[The height of the applet, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Space on each side of the applet, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfgrid">
					<help><![CDATA[Used inside cfform, cfgrid lets you place a grid control in a form. A grid control is 
  	a table of data divided into rows and columns. The cfgrid tag column data is specified with cfgridcolumn tags.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="target">
							<help><![CDATA[Target attribute for href URL.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[Width value of the grid control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="textcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Color value for text in the grid control. Options are: black (default), magenta, cyan, orange, darkgray, 
		pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow. A hex value can be entered in the form: textColor = "##xxxxxx" where x is 0-9 or A-F. Use two 
		pound signs or no pound signs.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="notsupported">
							<help><![CDATA[Selection mode for items in the grid control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[Height value of the grid control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="autowidth">
							<help><![CDATA[Optional. Yes or No. Default is No.
	If Yes, automatically sets the width of each column so that all the columns are visible within the 
	grid's specified width. All columns are initially set to equal widths. Users can resize any column. 
	No horizontal scroll bars are available since all columns are visible.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaders">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays a column of numeric row labels in the grid control. 
		Defaults to Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaders">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays column headers in the grid control. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes displays grid control text in boldface. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="insertbutton">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to use for the Insert action button. The default is Insert.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sortascendingbutton">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to use for the Sort button. Default is "A - Z".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="deletebutton">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to use for the delete action button. The default is delete.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaderbold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays row label text in boldface. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="selectmode">
							<help><![CDATA[Selection mode for items in the grid control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="insert">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes lets end users insert row data into the grid. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the grid element.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onvalidate">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a JavaScript function used to validate user input. The form object, input object, 
		and input object value are passed to the routine, which should return True if validation succeeds and 
		False otherwise.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="gridlines">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes enables row and column rules (lines) in the grid control. No suppresses rules. 
		Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaderfontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Size for column header text in the grid control, in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of rows to display in the grid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="italic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes displays grid control text in italic. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="href">
							<help><![CDATA[URL to associate with the grid item or a query column for a grid that is populated from a query.
		If href is a query column, the href value is populated by the query. If href is not recognized as a 
		query column, it is assumed that the href text is an actual HTML href.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Font size for text in the grid control, in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="picturebar">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. If Yes, images are used for the Insert, delete, and Sort buttons rather than text. 
		Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onblur">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaderalign">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter Left, Right, or Center to position data within a row header. Default is Left.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help><![CDATA[Height value of the grid control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Horizontal margin spacing to the left and right of the grid control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onerror">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a JavaScript function to execute in the event of a failed validation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheadertextcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Color value for the grid control column headers. Valid entries are: black (default), magenta, 
		cyan, orange, darkgray, pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow.A hex value can be entered in the form: 
		colHeaderTextColor = "##xxxxxx" 
		where x is 0-9 or A-F. Use either two pound signs or no pound signs.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheight">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of pixels for the minimum row height of the grid control. Used with cfgridcolumn 
		type = "Image", you can use rowHeight to define enough space for graphics to display in the row.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaderitalic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays row label text in italic. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="griddataalign">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter Left, Right, or Center to position data in the grid within a column. Default is Left.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaderfont">
							<help><![CDATA[Font for the column header in the grid control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaderalign">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter Left, Right, or Center to position data within a column header. Default is Left.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delete">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes lets end users delete row data from the grid. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hrefkey">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a query column when the grid uses a query. The column specified becomes the Key 
		regardless of the select mode for the grid.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaderwidth">
							<help><![CDATA[The width, in pixels, of the row header column.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaderitalic">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays column header text in italic. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheadertextcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Text color value for the grid control row headers. Entries are: black (default), magenta, cyan, 
		orange, darkgray, pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow. A hex value can be entered in the form: rowHeaderTextColor = "##xxxxxx" 
		Where x is 0-9 or A-F. Use two pound signs or no pound signs.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="selectcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Background color for a selected item. See bgColor for color options.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="vspace">
							<help><![CDATA[Vertical margin spacing above and below the grid control, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="appendkey">
							<help><![CDATA[When used with href, Yes passes query string value of the selected tree item in the URL to the
		application page specified in the cfform action attribute. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colheaderbold">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes displays column header text in boldface. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onfocus">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help><![CDATA[Alignment value. Options are: Top, Left, Bottom, Baseline, Texttop, Absbottom, Middle, 
	Absmiddle, Right.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaderfontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[Size for row label text in the grid control, in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="font">
							<help><![CDATA[Font to use for column data in the grid control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="highlighthref">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes highlights links associated with a cfgrid with an href attribute value. No disables
		highlight. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sort">
							<help><![CDATA[If Yes, sort buttons are added to the grid control. When clicked, sort buttons perform a simple 
	text sort on the selected column. Default is No.
	Note that columns are sortable by clicking the column head, even if no sort button is displayed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the query associated with the grid control.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bgcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Background color value for the grid control. Entries are: black, magenta, cyan, 
		orange, darkgray, pink, gray, white, lightgray, yellow. A hex value can be entered in the form: bgColor = "##xxxxxx"
		where x is 0-9 or A-F. Use either two pound signs or no pound signs.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sortdescendingbutton">
							<help><![CDATA[Text to use for the Sort button. Default is "Z - A".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rowheaderfont">
							<help><![CDATA[Font to use for the row label.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onchange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfajaxproxy">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cffeed">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="overwriteenclosure">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overwrite">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enclosuredir">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="properties">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ignoreenclosureerror">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="useragent">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="outputfile">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="xmlvar">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="columnmap">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfstopwatch">
					<help><![CDATA[Stops the time from starttag to endtag]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of variable to write time to it]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="label">
							<help><![CDATA[Label of the stopwatch]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfchartseries">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with the cfchart and cfchartseries tags. This tag defines chart data points. Its data is submitted to the cfchartseries tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="colorlist">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datalabelstyle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="markerstyle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="seriescolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="paintstyle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="itemcolumn">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuecolumn">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="serieslabel">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfheader">
					<help><![CDATA[Generates custom HTTP response headers to return to the client.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="statustext">
							<help><![CDATA[Text that explains the status code. This attribute is used in conjunction with the 
	statusCode attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the header.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[A value for the HTTP header. This attribute is used in conjunction with the name attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="statuscode">
							<help><![CDATA[A number that sets the HTTP status code.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcatch">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines table column header, width, alignment, and text. Used only inside a cftable.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[name for variable, by default it is cfcatch]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of catch, default:Any]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfthrow">
					<help><![CDATA[The cfthrow tag raises a developer-specified exception that can be caught with cfcatch tag 
  having any of the following type specifications - cfcatch type = 'custom_type', cfcatch type = 'Application'
  'cfcatch' type = 'Any']]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="errorcode">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom error code that you supply.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="object">
							<help><![CDATA[a native java exception Object, if this attribute is defined all other will be ignored]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom type or the predefined type Application. Do not enter any other predefined types because 
		they are not generated by CFML applications. If you specify the exception type Application, you 
		need not specify a type for cfcatch, because the Application type is the default cfcatch type]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="detail">
							<help><![CDATA[A detailed description of the event. The CFML server appends the position of the error to 
		this description; the server uses this parameter if an error is not caught by your code.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="message">
							<help><![CDATA[A message that describes the exceptional event.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="extendedinfo">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom error code that you supply.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfassociate">
					<help><![CDATA[Allows subtag data to be saved with the base tag. Applies only to custom tags.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="datacollection">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the structure in which the base tag stores subtag data.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="basetag">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of the base tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflayoutarea">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflayout">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfelseif">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with cfelse and cfelseif, 
			cfif lets you create simple and compound conditional statements 
			in CFML. The value in the cfif tag can be any expression.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="contition">
							<help><![CDATA[Expression Contition]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfdump">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfhttp">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you execute HTTP POST and GET operations on files. Using cfhttp, you can execute standard 
  GET operations and create a query object from a text file. POST operations lets you upload MIME file 
  types to a server, or post cookie, formfield, URL, file, or CGI variables directly to a specified server.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="addtoken">
							<help><![CDATA[if yes add urltoken as cookie]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid username.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a server, a valid password.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="columns">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the column names for a query when creating a query as a result of a cfhttp GET.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="textqualifier">
							<help><![CDATA[Required for creating a query. Indicates the start and finish of a column. Should be 
	appropriately escaped when embedded in a column. For example, if the qualifier is a double quotation 
	mark, it should be escaped as """". If there is no text qualifier in the file, specify it as " ". 
	Default is the double quotation mark (").]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="method">
							<help><![CDATA[GET or POST. Use GET to download a text or binary file or to create a query from the contents 
	of a text file. Use POST to send information to a server page or a CGI program for processing. POST 
	requires the use of a cfhttpparam tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help><![CDATA[set the charset for the call.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a server, a valid username.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="url">
							<help><![CDATA[Full URL of the host name or IP address of the server on which the file resides. The URL must be
	an absolute URL, including the protocol (http or https) and hostname. It may optionally contain a port
	number. Port numbers specified in the url attribute override the port attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="throwonerror">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to throw an exception that can be caught by using the cftry and 
	cfcatch tags. The default is NO.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[A value, in seconds. When a URL timeout is specified in the browser, the timeout attribute setting 
		takes precedence over the Railo Administrator timeout. The server then uses the lesser 
		of the URL timeout and the timeout passed in the timeout attribute, so that the request always times 
		out before or at the same time as the page times out. If there is no URL timeout specified, Railo 
		takes the lesser of the Railo Administrator timeout and the timeout passed in the timeout attribute.
		If there is no timeout set on the URL in the browser, no timeout set in the Railo Administrator, 
		and no timeout set with the timeout attribute, Railo waits indefinitely for the cfhttp request to 
		process.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the server from which the object is requested. Default is 80. When used with 
	resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically resolved to 
	preserve links in the retrieved document. If a port number is specified in the url attribute, the port
	value overrides the value of the port attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[return variable name, default "cfhhtp"]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help><![CDATA[The port number on the proxy server from which the object is requested. Default is 80. When 
	used with resolveURL, the URLs of retrieved documents that specify a port number are automatically 
	resolved to preserve links in the retrieved document.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="getasbinary">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="multiparttype">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="redirect">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to redirect execution or stop execution. The default is Yes. If set 
	to No and throwOnError = "yes", execution stops if cfhttp fails, and the status code and associated 
	error message are returned in the variable cfhttp.statuscode. To see where execution would have been 
	redirected, use the variable cfhttp.responseHeader[LOCATION]. The key LOCATION identifies the path of 
	redirection. Railo will follow up to five redirections on a request. if this limit is exceeded, 
	Railo behaves as if redirect = "no".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help><![CDATA[When required by a proxy server, a valid password.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="multipart">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="path">
							<help><![CDATA[The path to the directory in which a file is to be stored. If a path is not specified in a POST 
	or GET operation, a variable is created (cfhttp.fileContent) that you can use to display the results 
	of the POST operation in a cfoutput.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="firstrowasheaders">
							<help><![CDATA[sets if first row of csv is file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="useragent">
							<help><![CDATA[User agent request header.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name or IP address of a proxy server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="resolveurl">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Default is No. For GET and POST operations, if Yes, page reference returned into the 
	fileContent internal variable has its internal URLs fully resolved, including port number, so that 
	links remain intact.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[The filename to be used for the file that is accessed. For GET operations, defaults to the name 
	pecified in url. Enter path information in the path attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiter">
							<help><![CDATA[Required for creating a query. Options are a tab or comma. Default is a comma.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[The name to assign to a query if the a query is constructed from a file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cftreeitem">
					<help><![CDATA[Populates a tree control, created with cftree, with elements. You can use the img values 
  supplied with CFML or reference your own icons.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="href">
							<help><![CDATA[URL to associate with the tree item or a query column for a tree that is populated from a query. 
	If href is a query column, the href value is the value populated by the query. If href is not 
	recognized as a query column, it is assumed that the href text is an actual HTML href.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="img">
							<help><![CDATA[Image name or filename for the tree item. When populating a cftree with data from a cfquery, 
	images or filenames for each level of the tree are specified in a comma-separated list.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="target">
							<help><![CDATA[Target attribute for href URL. When populating a cftree with data from a cfquery, targets are specified in a 
	comma-separated list.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="display">
							<help><![CDATA[The label for the tree item. Default is value. When populating a cftree with data from a 
	cfquery, display names are specified in a comma-separated list.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Query name used to generate data for the treeitem.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="queryasroot">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Defines specified query as the root level. As in Example 1, this option avoids 
	having to create an additional parent cftreeitem. If you specify a text string other than Yes or 
	No, the tag uses the text as the root text.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="imgopen">
							<help><![CDATA[Icon displayed with open tree item. You can specify the icon filename using a relative path.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Value passed when the cfform is submitted. When populating a cftree with data from a 
	cfquery, columns are specified in a comma-separated list.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="expand">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes expands tree to show tree item children. No keeps tree item collapsed. 
	Default is Yes]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="parent">
							<help><![CDATA[Value for tree item parent.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfforward">
					<help><![CDATA[forward the request to a other path.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="template">
							<help><![CDATA[template path to forward to]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfabort">
					<help><![CDATA[Stops processing of a page at the tag location. CFML returns everything that was processed before the cfabort tag. The cfabort tag is often used with conditional logic to stop processing a page when a condition occurs.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[define if only current page execution will aborted or the hole request.
				values are "page" for the curretn page or "request" for all.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showerror">
							<help><![CDATA[The error to display when cfabort executes. 
				The error message displays in the standard CFML error page.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflogin">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="cookiedomain">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="applicationtoken">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="idletimeout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfmapitem">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflock">
					<help><![CDATA[Provides two types of locks to ensure the integrity of shared data: Exclusive lock and Read-only 
  lock. An exclusive lock single-threads access to the CFML constructs in its body. Single-threaded access 
  implies that the body of the tag can be executed by at most one request at a time. A request executing 
  inside a cflock tag has an "exclusive lock" on the tag. No other requests can start executing inside the 
  tag while a request has an exclusive lock. Railo issues exclusive locks on a first-come, first-served 
  basis. A read-only lock allows multiple requests to access the CFML constructs inside its body concurrently. 
  Therefore, read-only locks should be used only when the shared data is read only and not modified. If another 
  request already has an exclusive lock on the shared data, the request waits for the exclusive lock to be 
  released.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the lock. Only one request can execute inside a cflock tag with a given 
	name. Therefore, providing the name attribute allows for synchronizing access to resources from 
	different parts of an application. Lock names are global to a server. They are shared 
	between applications and user sessions, but not across clustered servers. This attribute is mutually 
	exclusive with the scope attribute. Therefore, do not specify the scope attribute and the name attribute 
	in a tag. The value of name cannot be an empty string.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[readOnly or Exclusive. Specifies the type of lock: read-only or exclusive. Default is Exclusive. 
	A read-only lock allows more than one request to read shared data. An exclusive lock allows only one 
	request to read or write to shared data.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scope">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the scope as one of the following: Application, Server, or Session. This attribute is mutually 
	exclusive with the name attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum amount of time, in seconds, to wait to obtain a lock. If a lock can be 
		obtained within the specified period, execution continues inside the body of the tag. Otherwise, the 
		behavior depends on the value of the throwOnTimeout attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="throwontimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Specifies how timeout conditions are handled. If the value is Yes, an exception is 
	generated to provide notification of the timeout. If the value is No, execution continues past the 
   cfclock tag. Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfregistry">
					<help><![CDATA[Reads, writes, and deletes keys and values in the system registry. The cfregistry tag is supported 
  on all platforms, including Linux, Solaris, and HP-UX.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[Variable into which to put value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of record set to contain returned keys and values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sort">
							<help><![CDATA[Sorts query column data (case-insensitive). Sorts on Entry, Type, and Value columns as text. Specify a combination of columns from query output, in a comma-delimited list. For example: 
sort = "value desc, entry asc"

asc: ascending (a to z) sort order 
desc: descending (z to a) sort order]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[string: return string values 
dWord: return DWord values 
key: return keys 
any: return keys and values]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="branch">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of a registry branch.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="entry">
							<help><![CDATA[Registry value to access.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[action to the registry]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Value data to set. If you omit this attribute, cfregistry creates default value, as follows:

string: creates an empty string: "" 
dWord: creates a value of 0 (zero)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfflush">
					<help><![CDATA[Flushes currently available data to the client.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="interval">
							<help><![CDATA[Flush the output each time at least the specified number of bytes become available. HTML 
		headers, and any data that is already available when you make this call, are not included in 
		the count.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfpdf">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="copyfrom">
							<help><![CDATA[Pathname of the PDF document from which to use the first page as a watermark]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[action to take]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pages">
							<help><![CDATA[Page or pages in the source PDF document on which to perform the action. You can specify multiple pages and page ranges as follows: "1,6-9,56-89,100, 110-120".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="image">
							<help><![CDATA[Image used as a watermark. You can specify a pathname, a variable that contains an image file, or a image variable]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="inputfiles">
							<help><![CDATA[Structure that maps the PDF source files to the input variables in the DDX file, or a string of elements and their pathname.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="permissions">
							<help><![CDATA[type of permissions on the PDF document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[PDF document variable name]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="destination">
							<help><![CDATA[Pathname of the modified PDF document. If the destination file exists, you must set the overwrite attribute to yes. If the destination file does not exist, CFML creates the file, if the parent directory exists.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showonprint">
							<help><![CDATA[Specify whether to print the watermark with the PDF document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="saveoption">
							<help><![CDATA[Save options for the PDF output]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ddxfile">
							<help><![CDATA[Pathname of the DDX file, or a string with DDX instructions]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="newownerpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[Password used to set permissions on a PDF document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help><![CDATA[PDF document used as the source.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="directory">
							<help><![CDATA[Directory of the PDF documents to merge. You must specify either the directory attribute or the source attribute. If you specify the directory attribute, CFML orders the documents by filename in descending order, by default. To change the order of the files, use the order attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ascending">
							<help><![CDATA[Order in which the PDF files are sorted]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="flatten">
							<help><![CDATA[Applies to forms created in Acrobat only (not forms created in LiveCycle); specifies whether interactivity is turned off]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help><![CDATA[File type of thumbnail image output]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="keepbookmark">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether bookmarks from the source PDF documents are retained in the merged document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="rotation">
							<help><![CDATA[Degree of rotation of the watermark image on the page.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scale">
							<help><![CDATA[Size of the thumbnail relative to the source page. The value represents a percentage from 1 through 100.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="outputfiles">
							<help><![CDATA[Structure that contains the output files in the DDX file or string as keys and the pathname to the result file as the value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[Owner or user password of the source PDF document, if the document is password-protected.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="filter">
							<help><![CDATA[file filter, used with attribute directory]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="foreground">
							<help><![CDATA[Placement of the watermark on the page]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="order">
							<help><![CDATA[Order in which the PDF documents in the directory are merged]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="position">
							<help><![CDATA[Position on the page where the watermark is placed. The position represents the top-left corner of the watermark. Specify the x and y coordinates; for example "50,30".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overwrite">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether PDF output overwrites the destination file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="resolution">
							<help><![CDATA[Image quality used to generate thumbnail images]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="newuserpassword">
							<help><![CDATA[Password used to open PDF document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="transparent">
							<help><![CDATA[(format="png" only) Specifies whether the image background is transparent or opaque]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="imageprefix">
							<help><![CDATA[prefix used for each image thumbnail file generated. The image filenames use the format: imagePrefix_page_n.format.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="opacity">
							<help><![CDATA[Opacity of the watermark. Valid values are integers in the range 0 (transparent) through 10 (opaque).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="isbase64">
							<help><![CDATA[Valid only when the image attribute is specified. Specifies whether the image used as a watermark is in Base64 format]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="version">
							<help><![CDATA[Version of the PDF used to write the document]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="info">
							<help><![CDATA[Structure variable for relevant information]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="encrypt">
							<help><![CDATA[Encryption type for the PDF output file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="stoponerror">
							<help><![CDATA[Valid only if the directory attribute is specified. If the specified directory contains files other then readable PDF files, Railo either stops merge process or continues.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfcollection">
					<help><![CDATA[Allows you to create and administer Search collections.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="categories">
							<help><![CDATA[Used only for creating a collection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the action to perform.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="path">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="collection">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies a collection name or an alias if action = "map"]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="language">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfprocresult">
					<help><![CDATA[Specifies a result set name that other tags, such as cfoutput and cftable, use to access 
  the result set. It also lets you optionally identify which of the stored procedure's result sets to 
  return. The cfprocresult tag is nested within a cfstoredproc tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name for the query result set.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum number of rows returned in the result set. The default is to return 
	all rows in the result set.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="resultset">
							<help><![CDATA[Identifies the desired result set if the stored procedure returns multiple result sets. 
		Default is 1.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfproperty">
					<help><![CDATA[Defines components as complex types that are used for web services authoring. The attributes of this tag are exposed as component metadata and are subject to inheritance rules.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A string; a property name. Must be a static value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="access">
							<help><![CDATA[The client security context from which the method can be invoked]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="setter">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hint">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="displayname">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="required">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[A string; a property type name; data type.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="getter">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="default">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfloop">
					<help><![CDATA[Looping is a very powerful programming technique that lets you repeat a set of instructions or 
  display output repeatedly until one or more conditions are met. cfloop supports five types of loops.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="characters">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="endline">
							<help><![CDATA[end line]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="to">
							<help><![CDATA[Ending value of index.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="charset">
							<help><![CDATA[charset for read the file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Query that controls the loop.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiters">
							<help><![CDATA[Character(s) that separates items in list]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="step">
							<help><![CDATA[Step by which to increment or decrement the index value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="index">
							<help><![CDATA[Index value. Railo sets it to from value and increments or decrements by step value, until it equals to value.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="array">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="endrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Last row of query that is included in the loop.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startline">
							<help><![CDATA[start line]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="collection">
							<help><![CDATA[Collection to loop over]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="from">
							<help><![CDATA[Beginning value of index.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[First row of query that is included in the loop.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="condition">
							<help><![CDATA[Condition that controls the loop.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="list">
							<help><![CDATA[A list, variable, or file name; contains a list]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="item">
							<help><![CDATA[Key for the collection]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="file">
							<help><![CDATA[file path]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cferror">
					<help><![CDATA[Enables the display of customized HTML pages when errors occur. This lets you maintain a 
  consistent look and feel within your application, even when errors occur.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="mailto">
							<help><![CDATA[The e-mail address of the administrator to notify of the error. The value
	is available to your custom error page in the MailTo property of the error object.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="exception">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of exception. Required if type = "exception" or "monitor".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[The type of error that the custom error page handles.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="template">
							<help><![CDATA[The relative path to the custom error page.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfsetting">
					<help><![CDATA[Controls various aspects of page processing, such as the output of HTML code in pages. One 
  benefit of this option is managing whitespace that can occur in output pages served by CFML.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="enablecfoutputonly">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. When set to Yes, cfsetting blocks output of HTML that resides outside cfoutput tags.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="requesttimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Integer; number of seconds. Time limit, after which CFML processes the page as an unresponsive thread. 
			Overrides the timeout set in the Railo Administrator.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showdebugoutput">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. When set to No, showDebugOutput suppresses debugging information that would 
		otherwise display at the end of the generated page.Default is Yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfimage">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you resize and add labels to GIF and JPEG format images.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="thickness">
							<help><![CDATA[Border thickness in pixels. The border is added to the outside edge of the source image, increasing the image area accordingly.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="isbase64">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether the source is a Base64 string]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="overwrite">
							<help><![CDATA[If the destination file already exists, Railo generates an error if the overwrite action is not set to yes.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fonts">
							<help><![CDATA[One or more valid fonts to use for the CAPTCHA text. Separate multiple fonts with commas. 
			Railo supports only the system fonts that the JDK can recognize. For example, TTF fonts in the Windows directory are supported on Windows.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="structname">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the structure to be created.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the structure to be created (alias for structname).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="quality">
							<help><![CDATA[Quality of the JPEG destination file. Applies only to files with an extension of JPG or JPEG. Valid values are fractions that range from 0 through 1 (the lower the number, the lower the quality).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="text">
							<help><![CDATA[Text string displayed in the CAPTCHA image. Use capital letters for better readability. Do not include spaces because users cannot detect them in the resulting CAPTCHA image.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passthrough">
							<help><![CDATA[HTML attributes that are not explicitly supported by cfimage. 
				If you specify an attribute and value, 
				they are passed to the tag "img".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help><![CDATA[Height in pixels of the image.
			For the resize attribute, you also can specify the height as a percentage.
			When you resize an image, if you specify a value for the width.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help><![CDATA[Width in pixels of the image.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help><![CDATA[source file]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="destination">
							<help><![CDATA[Absolute or relative pathname where the image output is written. 
				The image format is determined by the file extension.
				The convert and write actions require a destination attribute. 
				The border, captcha, resize, and rotate actions require a name attribute or a destination attribute. 
				You can specify both.
				If you do not enter a destination, 
				the CAPTCHA image is placed inline in the HTML output and displayed in the web browser.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="color">
							<help><![CDATA[Border color. Hexadecimal value or supported named color. For a hexadecimal value, use the form "#xxxxxx" or "xxxxxx", where x = 0-9 or A-F; use two number signs or none.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Action to execute. Must be one of the following:
			border, captcha, convert, info, read, resize, rotate, write, writeToBrowser
			The default action is read, which you do not need to specify explicitly.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help><![CDATA[Format of the image displayed in the browser. 
			If you do not specify a format, the image is displayed in PNG format.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="difficulty">
							<help><![CDATA[Level of complexity of the CAPTCHA text. 
			Specify one of the following levels of text distortion:
			low, medium, high]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="angle">
							<help><![CDATA[Angle in degrees to rotate the image.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help><![CDATA[font size of the text in the CAPTCHA image.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the image variable to create.
			The read action requires a name attribute.
			The border, resize, and rotate actions require a name attribute or a destination attribute. 
			You can specify both.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfobject">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you call methods in COM, CORBA, and JAVA objects.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="context">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="server">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="class">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="webservice">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyport">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="component">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiters">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="locale">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyuser">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxyserver">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="proxypassword">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfgraph">
					<help><![CDATA[Displays a graphical representation of data.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="showvaluelabel">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether values are displayed for the data points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="graphwidth">
							<help><![CDATA[Width of the graph, in pixels. Default is 320.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scaleto">
							<help><![CDATA[The maximum value of the graph value axis.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of chart to display.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="url">
							<help><![CDATA[A URL to load when the user clicks any data point on the chart.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the query containing the data to graph. Required if you do not use cfgraphdata tags in the cfgraph tag body to specify the data values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuelabelfont">
							<help><![CDATA[The font used to display data values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuelabelsize">
							<help><![CDATA[The size the value text, in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="titlefont">
							<help><![CDATA[The font used to display the title.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="urlcolumn">
							<help><![CDATA[Query column containing URL information to load when the user clicks the corresponding data point.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="colorlist">
							<help><![CDATA[Comma delimited list of colors to use for each data point.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showitemlabel">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to put item labels on the horizontal axis of bar charts and the vertical axis of HorizontalBar charts.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="legendfont">
							<help><![CDATA[The font used to display the legend.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="itemlabelfont">
							<help><![CDATA[The font used for the item labels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="itemlabelsize">
							<help><![CDATA[The size of the item labels, in points.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="borderwidth">
							<help><![CDATA[Border thickness, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fill">
							<help><![CDATA[Width of the graph line, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scalefrom">
							<help><![CDATA[The minimum value of the graph value axis (the vertical axis for Bar charts, the horizontal axis for HorizontalBar charts).]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="linewidth">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies whether to fill the area below the line with the line color to create an area graph.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuecolumn">
							<help><![CDATA[Query column that contains the data values.
      Required if you do not use cfgraphdata tags in the cfgraph tag body to specify the data values.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="itemcolumn">
							<help><![CDATA[Query column that contains the item label for the corresponding data point. The item labels appear in the chart legend.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bordercolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Border color.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="linecolor">
							<help><![CDATA[The color used to draw the data line.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="valuelocation">
							<help><![CDATA[Where value labels are placed.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showlegend">
							<help><![CDATA[The placement of the legend that identifies colors with the data labels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fileformat">
							<help><![CDATA[File type to be used for the output displayed in the browser.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="graphheight">
							<help><![CDATA[Height of the graph, in pixels. Default is 240.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="itemlabelorientation">
							<help><![CDATA[Orientation of item labels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="barspacing">
							<help><![CDATA[Spacing between bars in the chart, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="depth">
							<help><![CDATA[Depth of 3D chart appearance, in pixels.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="backgroundcolor">
							<help><![CDATA[Color of the chart background.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="gridlines">
							<help><![CDATA[An integer that specifies the number of grid lines to display on the chart between the top and bottom lines.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help><![CDATA[Title to display centered above the chart, or below the chart if the legend is above the chart.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfchartdata">
					<help><![CDATA[Used with the cfchart and cfchartseries tags. This tag defines chart data points. Its data is submitted to the cfchartseries tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="item">
							<help><![CDATA[string; data point name]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[number or expression; data point value]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfhtmlhead">
					<help><![CDATA[Writes the text specified in the text attribute to the 'head' section of a generated HTML page. 
	 The cfhtmlhead tag can be useful for embedding JavaScript code, or placing other HTML tags such, as 
	 META, LINK, TITLE, or BASE in an HTML page header.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of variable to contain the text for htmlhead.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Type of file manipulation that the tag performs.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="text">
							<help><![CDATA[The text to add to the 'head' area of an HTML page. Everything inside the quotation marks is 
		placed in the 'head' section]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfformgroup">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onchange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="selectedindex">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="label">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfqueryparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Checks the data type of a query parameter. The cfqueryparam tag is nested within a cfquery tag. 
  It is embedded within the query SQL statement. If you specify its optional parameters, cfqueryparam 
  also performs data validation.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="null">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Indicates whether the parameter is passed as a null. If Yes, the tag ignores the 
	value attribute. The default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cfsqltype">
							<help><![CDATA[The SQL type that the parameter (any type) will be bound to.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxlength">
							<help><![CDATA[Maximum length of the parameter. The default value is the length of the string specified in 
	the value attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="list">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Indicates that the parameter value of the value attribute is a list of values, 
	separated by a separator character. The default is No]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the actual value that Railo passes to the right of the comparison operator in a 
	where clause.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="separator">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the character that separates values in the list of parameter values in the value 
	attribute. The default is a comma. If you specify a list of values for the value attribute, you must 
	also specify the list attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scale">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of decimal places of the parameter. The default value is zero.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfprocparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Specifies parameter information, including type, name, value, and length. The cfprocparam tag 
  is nested within a cfstoredproc tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="null">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates whether the parameter is passed as a null. If you specify Yes, the tag ignores 
	the value attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="cfsqltype">
							<help><![CDATA[The SQL type that the parameter of any type is bound to.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[The variable name that you use to reference the value that the output parameter 
	represents after the call is made to the stored procedure.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxlength">
							<help><![CDATA[Maximum length of the parameter.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Indicates whether the passed variable is an input, output or input/output variable. Default is IN.
	The value IN passes the parameter by value. Values OUT and INOUT pass parameters as bound variables.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dbvarname">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[Corresponds to the actual value that Railo passes to the stored procedure.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scale">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of decimal places of the parameter.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfpop">
					<help><![CDATA[Retrieves and deletes e-mail messages from a POP mail server.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name for the index query.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="generateuniquefilenames">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to generate unique filenames for the files attached to an e-mail 
		message to avoid naming conflicts when the files are saved. Default is NO.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="attachmentpath">
							<help><![CDATA[Allows attachments to be written to the specified directory when action = "getAll". If an 
		invalid attachmentPath is specified, no attachment files are written to the server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[Defaults to the standard POP port, 110.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="server">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name biff.upperlip.com or IP address 192.1.2.225 of the POP server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the mail action.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="messagenumber">
							<help><![CDATA[Can be a comma-separated list of the message ids]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If no user name is specified, the POP connection is anonymous.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Sets the number of messages returned, starting with the number in the startRow attribute. 
		This attribute is ignored if messageNumber is specified.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="uid">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum time, in seconds, to wait for mail processing. Defaults is 60 seconds.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the first row number to be retrieved. Default is 1. This attribute is ignored if 
		messageNumber is specified.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[Password that corresponds to user name.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfwindow">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfpdfparam">
					<help><![CDATA[Provides additional information for the cfpdf tag. The cfpdfparam tag applies only to the merge action of the cfpdf tag and is always a child tag of the cfpdf tag.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="pages">
							<help><![CDATA[age or pages of the PDF source file to merge. You can specify a range of pages, for example, "1-5 ", or a comma-separated list of pages, for example, "1-5,9-10,18".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[User or owner password, if the source PDF file is password-protected.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="source">
							<help><![CDATA[Source PDF file to merge. You can specify a PDF variable, a cfdocument variable, or the pathname to a file.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfselect">
					<help><![CDATA[Used inside cfform, cfselect lets you construct a drop-down list box form control. You can 
  populate the drop-down list box from a query, or using the option tag. Use option elements to populate 
  lists. The syntax for the option tag is the same as for its HTML counterpart.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="lang">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passthrough">
							<help><![CDATA[HTML attributes that are not explicitly supported by cfselect. If you specify an attribute and 
		its value, the attribute and its value are passed to the HTML code that is generated for the cfselect 
		tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="size">
							<help><![CDATA[Number of entries in the drop-down list.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseover">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="message">
							<help><![CDATA[Message that displays if required = 'Yes' and no selection is made.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datafld">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="class">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the form you are creating.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="queryposition">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="required">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. If Yes, a list element must be selected when the form is submitted, and the size of 
		the drop-down list must be at least two. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ondblclick">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeydown">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="group">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dataformatas">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="display">
							<help><![CDATA[The query column displayed. Defaults to the value of value. Used with the query attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tabindex">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onblur">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="selected">
							<help><![CDATA[A value matching at least one entry in value to preselect the entry in the drop-down list box.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="casesensitive">
							<help><![CDATA[is compare for selected case sensitive or not]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onerror">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a valid JavaScript function to execute in the event of a failed validation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseup">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="disabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="multiple">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes permits selection of multiple elements in the drop-down list box. The default 
		is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmousedown">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onclick">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeypress">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="editable">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[The query column value for the list element. Used with the query attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmousemove">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="label">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datasrc">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onfocus">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseout">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeyup">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Name of the query to be used to populate the drop-down list box.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dir">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onchange">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfchart">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="yoffset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="xoffset">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="yaxistitle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="url">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="databackgroundcolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="yaxistype">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="foregroundcolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="markersize">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="backgroundcolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="seriesplacement">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="gridlines">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showmarkers">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontbold">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scalefrom">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="chartheight">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showborder">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="scaleto">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sortxaxis">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontsize">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pieslicestyle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tipbgcolor">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="format">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="chartwidth">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="xaxistype">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showxgridlines">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="labelformat">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="fontitalic">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="xaxistitle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showlegend">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="font">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="show3d">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tipstyle">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showygridlines">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfindex">
					<help><![CDATA[Populates collections with indexed data. The cfindex and cfsearch tags encapsulate the 
  indexing and searching utilities. Collections can be populated from text files in a directory 
  you specify, or from a query generated by a query. Before you can populate a collection, 
  you must create the collection using either the cfcollection tag or the Railo Administrator. Use 
  cfsearch to search collections you populate with cfindex.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="recurse">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. Yes specifies, if type = "Path", that directories below the path specified in 
	key are included in the indexing operation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="custom4">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom field you can use to store data during an indexing operation. 
			Usage is the same as for custom1.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="custom3">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom field you can use to store data during an indexing operation. 
			Usage is the same as for custom1.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="custom2">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom field you can use to store data during an indexing operation. Usage is the same as 
	for custom1.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the type of entity being indexed. Default is CUSTOM.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="custom1">
							<help><![CDATA[A custom field you can use to store data during an indexing operation. Specify a query column 
	name for type and a query name.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="query">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the name of the query against which the collection is generated.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="external">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[the timeout in seconds for a single request of type url]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="body">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="collection">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies a collection name. If you are indexing an external collection external = "Yes", 
	specify the collection name, including fully qualified path.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="language">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="status">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="category">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the index action.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="urlpath">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the URL path for files if type = "file" and type = "path". When the collection is 
	searched with cfsearch, the pathname is automatically be prepended to filenames and returned as 
	the url attribute.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="prefix">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="categorytree">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="extensions">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the comma-separated list of file extensions that Railo uses to index files if 
	type = "Path". Default is HTM, HTML, CFM, CFML, DBM, DBML.
	An entry of "*." returns files with no extension]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="throwontimeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies how timeout conditions are handled. If the value is true, an exception is enerated to provide notification of the timeout. If the value is No, execution continues. Default is no.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="key">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help><![CDATA[Title for collection;
Query column name for type and a valid query name;
Permits searching collections by title or displaying a separate title from the key]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfntauthenticate">
					<help/>
					
					
						<parameter name="result">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="listgroups">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="throwonerror">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="domain">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfwhile">
					<help><![CDATA[same like loop-contition but easier to use]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="condition">
							<help><![CDATA[Contition o the expression]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cflocation">
					<help><![CDATA[Opens a CFML page or HTML file. For example, you might use cflocation to specify a standard 
  message or response that you use in several applications. Use the addToken attribute to verify 
  client requests.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="url">
							<help><![CDATA[The URL of the HTML file or CFML page to open.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="statuscode">
							<help><![CDATA[statuscode used for the redirect (301 or 302)]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="addtoken">
							<help><![CDATA[Yes or No. clientManagement must be enabled, see cfapplication. Yes appends client variable 
		information to the URL you specify in the url.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfgridrow">
					<help><![CDATA[Lets you define a cfgrid that does not use a query as source for row data. If a query attribute is
  specified in cfgrid, the cfgridrow tags are ignored.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="data">
							<help><![CDATA[A comma-separated list of column values. If a column value contains a comma character, 
	it must be escaped with a second comma character.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfstylesheet">
					<help/>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfmodule">
					<help><![CDATA[Invokes a custom tag for use in cfml templates. The cfmodule tag can help deal with 
  custom tag name conflicts. Use the template attribute to name a template that contains the custom 
  tag definition, including its path..]]></help>
					
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfinput">
					<help><![CDATA[Used inside cfform to place radio buttons, checkboxes, or text boxes. Provides input 
  validation for the specified control type.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="onselect">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onselect]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="validate">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="showautosuggestloadingicon">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="firstdayofweek">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="required">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter Yes or No. Default is No.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tabindex">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute tabIndex]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="passthrough">
							<help><![CDATA[HTML attributes that are not explicitly supported by cfinput. 
				If you specify an attribute and value, 
				they are passed to the HTML code generated for the cfinput tag.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="enabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="pattern">
							<help><![CDATA[The JavaScript regular expression pattern to use to validate the input. Required only if you 
	specify validate = "regular_expression".]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onerror">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a JavaScript function you want to execute in the event of a failed validation.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="accept">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseover">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onMouseOver]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="autosuggestbinddelay">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmousedown">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onMouseDown]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="label">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onblur">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onBlur]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="title">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="border">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="height">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dir">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bindonload">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="visible">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="tooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="notab">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxresultsdisplayed">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onvalidate">
							<help><![CDATA[The name of a JavaScript function used to validate user input. The form object, input object, 
	and input object value are passed to the specified routine, which should return true if validation 
	succeeds and false otherwise. If used, the validate attribute is ignored.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onfocus">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onFocus]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="message">
							<help><![CDATA[Message text to appear if validation fails.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datasrc">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="range">
							<help><![CDATA[Enter a minimum and maximum value range, separated by a comma. Valid only for numeric data.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="src">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="size">
							<help><![CDATA[The size of the input control. Ignored if type is Radio or Checkbox.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[An initial value for the form input element.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="lang">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bindattribute">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseout">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onMouseOut]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="validateat">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmouseup">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onMouseUp]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeyup">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onKeyUp]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="id">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute id]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeydown">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onKeyDown]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ismap">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="usemap">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onkeypress">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onKeyPress]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="style">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute style]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="ondblclick">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onDblclick]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onmousemove">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onMouseMove]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onclick">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onClick]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="mask">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="typeahead">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[A name for the form input element.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="dataformatas">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="accesskey">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="daynames">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onbinderror">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="autosuggestminlength">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="delimiter">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="datafld">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="readonly">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="disabled">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="width">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="checked">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="alt">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="hspace">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="class">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute class]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="monthnames">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="bind">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="onchange">
							<help><![CDATA[the html attribute onChange]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="sourcefortooltip">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="autosuggest">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="align">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxlength">
							<help><![CDATA[The maximum length of text entered, if n type is Text.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfxml">
					<help><![CDATA[Creates a CFML XML document object that contains the markup in the tag body. This tag can include XML and CFML tags. 
		Railo processes the CFML code in the tag body, then assigns the resulting text to an XML document object variable.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[name of an xml variable]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="casesensitive">
							<help><![CDATA[yes: maintains the case of document elements and attributes]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="validator">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfservletparam">
					<help><![CDATA[This tag has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="variable">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="type">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="value">
							<help><![CDATA[This attribute has been deprecated and is non-functional.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfimap">
					<help><![CDATA[Retrieves and deletes e-mail messages from a Imap mail server.]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="name">
							<help><![CDATA[Name for the index query.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="generateuniquefilenames">
							<help><![CDATA[Boolean indicating whether to generate unique filenames for the files attached to an e-mail 
		message to avoid naming conflicts when the files are saved. Default is NO.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="attachmentpath">
							<help><![CDATA[Allows attachments to be written to the specified directory when action = "getAll". If an 
		invalid attachmentPath is specified, no attachment files are written to the server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="port">
							<help><![CDATA[Defaults to the standard Imap port, 143.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="server">
							<help><![CDATA[Host name biff.upperlip.com or IP address 192.1.2.225 of the Imap server.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="action">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the mail action.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="messagenumber">
							<help><![CDATA[Can be a comma-separated list of the message ids]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="username">
							<help><![CDATA[If no user name is specified, the Imap connection is anonymous.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="maxrows">
							<help><![CDATA[Sets the number of messages returned, starting with the number in the startRow attribute. 
		This attribute is ignored if messageNumber is specified.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="uid">
							<help/>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="timeout">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the maximum time, in seconds, to wait for mail processing. Defaults is 60 seconds.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="startrow">
							<help><![CDATA[Specifies the first row number to be retrieved. Default is 1. This attribute is ignored if 
		messageNumber is specified.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
						<parameter name="password">
							<help><![CDATA[Password that corresponds to user name.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
				
				<tag name="cfsleep">
					<help><![CDATA[Pauses the execution of the page for a given interval]]></help>
					
					
						<parameter name="time">
							<help><![CDATA[Expressed in milli seconds.]]></help>
							<values/>
						</parameter>
						
					
					
				</tag>
				
		
	</tags>
	<functions>
		
				
			<function name="getmetadata"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagewrite"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawline"/>
		
				
			<function name="createodbcdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="rand"/>
		
				
			<function name="filereadline"/>
		
				
			<function name="rereplace"/>
		
				
			<function name="wrap"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayset"/>
		
				
			<function name="serializejson"/>
		
				
			<function name="min"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitytoquery"/>
		
				
			<function name="listsetat"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitmaskread"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesheardrawingaxis"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraycontains"/>
		
				
			<function name="throw"/>
		
				
			<function name="evaluatecomponent"/>
		
				
			<function name="stripcr"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileclose"/>
		
				
			<function name="getclientvariableslist"/>
		
				
			<function name="metaphone"/>
		
				
			<function name="mid"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawimage"/>
		
				
			<function name="_jsonarray"/>
		
				
			<function name="log"/>
		
				
			<function name="iif"/>
		
				
			<function name="expandpath"/>
		
				
			<function name="entityreload"/>
		
				
			<function name="dollarformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="second"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesetdrawingstroke"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageaddborder"/>
		
				
			<function name="queryaddrow"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsparseeurocurrency"/>
		
				
			<function name="find"/>
		
				
			<function name="nullvalue"/>
		
				
			<function name="urlencodedformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="val"/>
		
				
			<function name="yesnoformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettempdirectory"/>
		
				
			<function name="log10"/>
		
				
			<function name="ispdffile"/>
		
				
			<function name="filewrite"/>
		
				
			<function name="querydeleterow"/>
		
				
			<function name="removechars"/>
		
				
			<function name="getk2serverdoccountlimit"/>
		
				
			<function name="systemoutput"/>
		
				
			<function name="binarydecode"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitnot"/>
		
				
			<function name="urldecode"/>
		
				
			<function name="componentcacheclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettickcount"/>
		
				
			<function name="structisempty"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitynamearray"/>
		
				
			<function name="comparenocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagescaletofit"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayslice"/>
		
				
			<function name="threadterminate"/>
		
				
			<function name="setprofilestring"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachegetallids"/>
		
				
			<function name="getwriteableimageformats"/>
		
				
			<function name="getprofilestring"/>
		
				
			<function name="getlocalhostip"/>
		
				
			<function name="getauthuser"/>
		
				
			<function name="isxml"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayreverse"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageoverlay"/>
		
				
			<function name="evaluate"/>
		
				
			<function name="listindexexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="daysinmonth"/>
		
				
			<function name="dateformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="getlocaledisplayname"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileseek"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawarc"/>
		
				
			<function name="week"/>
		
				
			<function name="listlen"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileread"/>
		
				
			<function name="getsoapresponse"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsweek"/>
		
				
			<function name="structkeyexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="getexception"/>
		
				
			<function name="isboolean"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageclearrect"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlchildpos"/>
		
				
			<function name="valuelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="_createcomponent"/>
		
				
			<function name="_dump"/>
		
				
			<function name="datediff"/>
		
				
			<function name="sqr"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettemplatepath"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettoken"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesetbackgroundcolor"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitshln"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraycontainsnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageformats"/>
		
				
			<function name="structsort"/>
		
				
			<function name="refind"/>
		
				
			<function name="isbinary"/>
		
				
			<function name="setlocale"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachesetproperties"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayprepend"/>
		
				
			<function name="hash"/>
		
				
			<function name="encryptbinary"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageresize"/>
		
				
			<function name="isstruct"/>
		
				
			<function name="isinstanceof"/>
		
				
			<function name="trim"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesharpen"/>
		
				
			<function name="tostring"/>
		
				
			<function name="charsetencode"/>
		
				
			<function name="reverse"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayappend"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagecrop"/>
		
				
			<function name="getk2serverdoccount"/>
		
				
			<function name="isnumericdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormexecutequery"/>
		
				
			<function name="isimagefile"/>
		
				
			<function name="nowserver"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagepaste"/>
		
				
			<function name="listrest"/>
		
				
			<function name="truefalseformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="listavg"/>
		
				
			<function name="structfindkey"/>
		
				
			<function name="cacheremove"/>
		
				
			<function name="transactionrollback"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettimezoneinfo"/>
		
				
			<function name="iscustomfunction"/>
		
				
			<function name="queryslice"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagetranslatedrawingaxis"/>
		
				
			<function name="issimplevalue"/>
		
				
			<function name="isuserinanyrole"/>
		
				
			<function name="findnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraynew"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitmaskset"/>
		
				
			<function name="duplicate"/>
		
				
			<function name="soundex"/>
		
				
			<function name="getvariable"/>
		
				
			<function name="decryptbinary"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsdateformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="htmlcodeformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlgetnodetype"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="parameterexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="getsoaprequest"/>
		
				
			<function name="componentinfo"/>
		
				
			<function name="toscript"/>
		
				
			<function name="randomize"/>
		
				
			<function name="listlast"/>
		
				
			<function name="listinsertat"/>
		
				
			<function name="setencoding"/>
		
				
			<function name="evaluatejava"/>
		
				
			<function name="querygetcell"/>
		
				
			<function name="dotnettocftype"/>
		
				
			<function name="cos"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormevictqueries"/>
		
				
			<function name="isuserinrole"/>
		
				
			<function name="getprofilesections"/>
		
				
			<function name="preservesinglequotes"/>
		
				
			<function name="urlsessionformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="ucfirst"/>
		
				
			<function name="struct"/>
		
				
			<function name="rjustify"/>
		
				
			<function name="pi"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraylast"/>
		
				
			<function name="binaryencode"/>
		
				
			<function name="ucase"/>
		
				
			<function name="urlencode"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayisdefined"/>
		
				
			<function name="max"/>
		
				
			<function name="rtrim"/>
		
				
			<function name="listdeleteat"/>
		
				
			<function name="abs"/>
		
				
			<function name="timeformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="listfirst"/>
		
				
			<function name="left"/>
		
				
			<function name="rematch"/>
		
				
			<function name="formatbasen"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageblur"/>
		
				
			<function name="_jsonstruct"/>
		
				
			<function name="dayofweek"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawcubiccurve"/>
		
				
			<function name="pagepoolclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="javacast"/>
		
				
			<function name="unserializejava"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmltransform"/>
		
				
			<function name="filesetlastmodified"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraysum"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraymin"/>
		
				
			<function name="getclasspath"/>
		
				
			<function name="replacelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegetwidth"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayindexexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawrect"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagenegative"/>
		
				
			<function name="listcompact"/>
		
				
			<function name="structkeytranslate"/>
		
				
			<function name="right"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagewritebase64"/>
		
				
			<function name="structappend"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagefonts"/>
		
				
			<function name="gethttptimestring"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegetheight"/>
		
				
			<function name="encrypt"/>
		
				
			<function name="extract"/>
		
				
			<function name="isk2serverdoccountexceeded"/>
		
				
			<function name="filewriteline"/>
		
				
			<function name="structupdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormflush"/>
		
				
			<function name="getrailoid"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileiseof"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormreload"/>
		
				
			<function name="gethttprequestdata"/>
		
				
			<function name="trace"/>
		
				
			<function name="isxmlnode"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageshear"/>
		
				
			<function name="getbasetagdata"/>
		
				
			<function name="len"/>
		
				
			<function name="exp"/>
		
				
			<function name="sleep"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitand"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitysave"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="tobase64"/>
		
				
			<function name="directoryexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsparsedatetime"/>
		
				
			<function name="queryconvertforgrid"/>
		
				
			<function name="isk2serverabroker"/>
		
				
			<function name="isk2serveronline"/>
		
				
			<function name="month"/>
		
				
			<function name="generatesecretkey"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayisempty"/>
		
				
			<function name="querycolumnarray"/>
		
				
			<function name="ispdfobject"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlvalidate"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageflip"/>
		
				
			<function name="query"/>
		
				
			<function name="verifyclient"/>
		
				
			<function name="location"/>
		
				
			<function name="getsoaprequestheader"/>
		
				
			<function name="getsysteminfo"/>
		
				
			<function name="replacenocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachegetmetadata"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagexordrawingmode"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsdayofweek"/>
		
				
			<function name="jsstringformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageread"/>
		
				
			<function name="rereplacenocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="lstimeformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="cfusion_encrypt"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagereadbase64"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagerotatedrawingaxis"/>
		
				
			<function name="getfunctiondata"/>
		
				
			<function name="array"/>
		
				
			<function name="directorylist"/>
		
				
			<function name="settimezone"/>
		
				
			<function name="sin"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsparsecurrency"/>
		
				
			<function name="rematchnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormgetsession"/>
		
				
			<function name="now"/>
		
				
			<function name="isddx"/>
		
				
			<function name="contractpath"/>
		
				
			<function name="isxmlattribute"/>
		
				
			<function name="paragraphformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="structget"/>
		
				
			<function name="getlocale"/>
		
				
			<function name="issoaprequest"/>
		
				
			<function name="listfind"/>
		
				
			<function name="listtoarray"/>
		
				
			<function name="repeatstring"/>
		
				
			<function name="getdirectoryfrompath"/>
		
				
			<function name="getsoapresponseheader"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawpoint"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsnumberformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="listappend"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayresize"/>
		
				
			<function name="listcontains"/>
		
				
			<function name="daysinyear"/>
		
				
			<function name="isjson"/>
		
				
			<function name="structkeyarray"/>
		
				
			<function name="directoryrename"/>
		
				
			<function name="querycolumnlist"/>
		
				
			<function name="imageinfo"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitxor"/>
		
				
			<function name="hour"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayfind"/>
		
				
			<function name="querycolumncount"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettagdata"/>
		
				
			<function name="tan"/>
		
				
			<function name="monthshortasstring"/>
		
				
			<function name="islocalhost"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayfirst"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagetranslate"/>
		
				
			<function name="sgn"/>
		
				
			<function name="chr"/>
		
				
			<function name="ctcacheclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="round"/>
		
				
			<function name="tobinary"/>
		
				
			<function name="listvaluecountnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="filecopy"/>
		
				
			<function name="quotedvaluelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileskipbytes"/>
		
				
			<function name="valuearray"/>
		
				
			<function name="isxmlroot"/>
		
				
			<function name="getencoding"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormevictcollection"/>
		
				
			<function name="datepart"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawroundrect"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayswap"/>
		
				
			<function name="day"/>
		
				
			<function name="listvaluecount"/>
		
				
			<function name="structcount"/>
		
				
			<function name="year"/>
		
				
			<function name="atn"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormclosesession"/>
		
				
			<function name="minute"/>
		
				
			<function name="filereadbinary"/>
		
				
			<function name="dateconvert"/>
		
				
			<function name="isimage"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachekeyexists"/>
		
				
			<function name="deserializejson"/>
		
				
			<function name="listprepend"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitmaskclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="decimalformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="directorydelete"/>
		
				
			<function name="getbasetemplatepath"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawbeveledrect"/>
		
				
			<function name="isleapyear"/>
		
				
			<function name="entityload"/>
		
				
			<function name="getgatewayhelper"/>
		
				
			<function name="getuserroles"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachecount"/>
		
				
			<function name="createdatetime"/>
		
				
			<function name="getfileinfo"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsisdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="parsenumber"/>
		
				
			<function name="millisecond"/>
		
				
			<function name="entityloadbypk"/>
		
				
			<function name="getcurrenttemplatepath"/>
		
				
			<function name="echo"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsiscurrency"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegetiptctag"/>
		
				
			<function name="asc"/>
		
				
			<function name="getreadableimageformats"/>
		
				
			<function name="componentcachelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlsearch"/>
		
				
			<function name="getnumericdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="isnumeric"/>
		
				
			<function name="createtime"/>
		
				
			<function name="randrange"/>
		
				
			<function name="numberformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="getmetricdata"/>
		
				
			<function name="listtrim"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraydelete"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraytostruct"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraymax"/>
		
				
			<function name="getprinterinfo"/>
		
				
			<function name="isnotmap"/>
		
				
			<function name="replace"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachedelete"/>
		
				
			<function name="dateadd"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawoval"/>
		
				
			<function name="structinsert"/>
		
				
			<function name="getbasetaglist"/>
		
				
			<function name="isxmlelem"/>
		
				
			<function name="structclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="spanincluding"/>
		
				
			<function name="cacheget"/>
		
				
			<function name="fileopen"/>
		
				
			<function name="querysort"/>
		
				
			<function name="filesetattribute"/>
		
				
			<function name="listitemtrim"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesetdrawingalpha"/>
		
				
			<function name="listqualify"/>
		
				
			<function name="structcopy"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraytolist"/>
		
				
			<function name="sendgatewaymessage"/>
		
				
			<function name="htmleditformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="sslcertificateinstall"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesetantialiasing"/>
		
				
			<function name="acos"/>
		
				
			<function name="createtimespan"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachegetproperties"/>
		
				
			<function name="cacheclear"/>
		
				
			<function name="traceobject"/>
		
				
			<function name="createguid"/>
		
				
			<function name="spanexcluding"/>
		
				
			<function name="dump"/>
		
				
			<function name="ljustify"/>
		
				
			<function name="insert"/>
		
				
			<function name="ltrim"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormgetsessionfactory"/>
		
				
			<function name="htmlparse"/>
		
				
			<function name="createodbcdatetime"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsparsenumber"/>
		
				
			<function name="writeoutput"/>
		
				
			<function name="inputbasen"/>
		
				
			<function name="getfunctionlist"/>
		
				
			<function name="newline"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegetblob"/>
		
				
			<function name="structnew"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesetdrawingcolor"/>
		
				
			<function name="datecompare"/>
		
				
			<function name="getpagecontext"/>
		
				
			<function name="getcurrentcontext"/>
		
				
			<function name="directorycreate"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayinsertat"/>
		
				
			<function name="compare"/>
		
				
			<function name="parsedatetime"/>
		
				
			<function name="fix"/>
		
				
			<function name="firstdayofmonth"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegetexiftag"/>
		
				
			<function name="isuserloggedin"/>
		
				
			<function name="cjustify"/>
		
				
			<function name="cacheput"/>
		
				
			<function name="precisionevaluate"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettempfile"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraylen"/>
		
				
			<function name="createobject"/>
		
				
			<function name="isdefined"/>
		
				
			<function name="getcomponentmetadata"/>
		
				
			<function name="decrypt"/>
		
				
			<function name="transactioncommit"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagesetdrawingtransparency"/>
		
				
			<function name="isobject"/>
		
				
			<function name="dayofweekasstring"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitydelete"/>
		
				
			<function name="threadjoin"/>
		
				
			<function name="createodbctime"/>
		
				
			<function name="de"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagenew"/>
		
				
			<function name="entityloadbyexample"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettimezone"/>
		
				
			<function name="isnull"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraydeleteat"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawquadraticcurve"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlnew"/>
		
				
			<function name="dayofyear"/>
		
				
			<function name="lsisnumeric"/>
		
				
			<function name="filesetaccessmode"/>
		
				
			<function name="pagepoollist"/>
		
				
			<function name="int"/>
		
				
			<function name="structfind"/>
		
				
			<function name="listcontainsnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="refindnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="getcontextroot"/>
		
				
			<function name="sslcertificatelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="iszipfile"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegrayscale"/>
		
				
			<function name="writedump"/>
		
				
			<function name="gettaglist"/>
		
				
			<function name="isvideofile"/>
		
				
			<function name="findoneof"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawtext"/>
		
				
			<function name="iswddx"/>
		
				
			<function name="structkeylist"/>
		
				
			<function name="listgetat"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlelemnew"/>
		
				
			<function name="structdelete"/>
		
				
			<function name="stringlen"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitymerge"/>
		
				
			<function name="isquery"/>
		
				
			<function name="releasecomobject"/>
		
				
			<function name="isxmldoc"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormclearsession"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachegetall"/>
		
				
			<function name="getfilefrompath"/>
		
				
			<function name="listfindnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="queryaddcolumn"/>
		
				
			<function name="cfusion_decrypt"/>
		
				
			<function name="cachegetdefaultcachename"/>
		
				
			<function name="createdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagegetbufferedimage"/>
		
				
			<function name="ctcachelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="compress"/>
		
				
			<function name="listchangedelims"/>
		
				
			<function name="isarray"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayavg"/>
		
				
			<function name="dayofweekshortasstring"/>
		
				
			<function name="structfindvalue"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitynew"/>
		
				
			<function name="listsort"/>
		
				
			<function name="lscurrencyformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="ajaxonload"/>
		
				
			<function name="quarter"/>
		
				
			<function name="ormevictentity"/>
		
				
			<function name="isdebugmode"/>
		
				
			<function name="querydeletecolumn"/>
		
				
			<function name="querynew"/>
		
				
			<function name="sizeof"/>
		
				
			<function name="incrementvalue"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitor"/>
		
				
			<function name="asin"/>
		
				
			<function name="filedelete"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagecopy"/>
		
				
			<function name="getvfsmetadata"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraysort"/>
		
				
			<function name="monthasstring"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagerotate"/>
		
				
			<function name="serialize"/>
		
				
			<function name="writelog"/>
		
				
			<function name="bitshrn"/>
		
				
			<function name="isipv6"/>
		
				
			<function name="lseurocurrencyformat"/>
		
				
			<function name="deleteclientvariable"/>
		
				
			<function name="querysetcell"/>
		
				
			<function name="lcase"/>
		
				
			<function name="beat"/>
		
				
			<function name="queryrecordcount"/>
		
				
			<function name="isvalid"/>
		
				
			<function name="xmlparse"/>
		
				
			<function name="isdate"/>
		
				
			<function name="createuuid"/>
		
				
			<function name="imagedrawlines"/>
		
				
			<function name="arraymerge"/>
		
				
			<function name="setvariable"/>
		
				
			<function name="filemove"/>
		
				
			<function name="entitynamelist"/>
		
				
			<function name="intergralcontext"/>
		
				
			<function name="ceiling"/>
		
				
			<function name="dumpstruct"/>
		
				
			<function name="decrementvalue"/>
		
				
			<function name="charsetdecode"/>
		
				
			<function name="arrayfindnocase"/>
		
				
			<function name="ajaxlink"/>
		
	</functions>
	
	<scopes/>
</dictionary>
